[{"year": 2024, "entities": [["Break My Dreams Nails", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["https://www.facebook.com/groups//?mibextid=NSMWBT", "NORP"]], "lemmas": ["join", "vip", "group", "nail", "enthusiast", "want", "easy", "cheap", "way", "level", "nail", "game", "access", "exclusive", "nail", "makeup", "hand", "nail", "care", "product", "plus", "expert", "tip", "trick", "help", "slay", "break", "free", "ordinary", "unleash", "creativity", "shopping", "link", "want", "browse", "link", "vip", "group"], "pos": [["Join", "VERB"], ["VIP", "NOUN"], ["group", "NOUN"], ["nail", "NOUN"], ["enthusiasts", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["easy", "ADJ"], ["cheap", "ADJ"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["level", "VERB"], ["nail", "NOUN"], ["game", "NOUN"], ["access", "NOUN"], ["exclusive", "ADJ"], ["nails", "NOUN"], ["makeup", "NOUN"], ["hand", "NOUN"], ["nail", "NOUN"], ["care", "NOUN"], ["products", "NOUN"], ["plus", "CCONJ"], ["expert", "NOUN"], ["tips", "NOUN"], ["tricks", "NOUN"], ["help", "VERB"], ["slay", "VERB"], ["Break", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["ordinary", "ADJ"], ["unleash", "VERB"], ["creativity", "NOUN"], ["shopping", "NOUN"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["browse", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["VIP", "NOUN"], ["group", "NOUN"]]}, {"year": 2023, "entities": [["the The Cozy Mystery Tribe", "ORG"], ["Original & LIFE SAVERS Gummies", "ORG"], ["TON", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["https://www.twitch.tv/breakmydreams", "PERSON"], ["Easter", "PERSON"], ["Topspace", "PERSON"], ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "PERSON"], ["Krispy Kreme", "PERSON"], ["Fallen Angel Costume", "PERSON"], ["Jaw Busters", "PERSON"], ["the Red Heart  ", "ORG"], ["Tallie", "PERSON"], ["at least $", "MONEY"], ["Peanut Butter Cookie:", "PERSON"], ["Gummy Candy Body Parts", "PERSON"], ["Remote Control Halloween Decorations Indoor", "ORG"], ["Jumpsuit forDolxico", "PERSON"], ["Strava", "GPE"], ["Headband WingPeach Costume", "FAC"], ["Hanging Witch with Bendable Arms", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Glow Gloves", "PERSON"], ["Amazon Mechanical Turk - $", "ORG"], ["the Crumble Cookies", "ORG"], ["Giveaways", "PERSON"], ["Inflatable Costumes for Kids", "ORG"], ["Mistborn TrilogyB. Sanderson", "PERSON"], ["ER", "ORG"], ["Trick or Treating, Cosplay PartyDouble Couple Halloween Costumes for Men Women with Scary Light up", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Port Points", "FAC"], ["Change of Fortune: A Fateful Force Origins Story", "ORG"], ["Scarecrow Costume", "PERSON"], ["all three", "CARDINAL"], ["CDnd", "NORP"], ["Gift Idea", "PERSON"], ["Otter", "PERSON"], ["Costume Party", "ORG"], ["Rewards", "NORP"], ["Magic Wand Remote - Floating Hanging Home Decorations", "PRODUCT"], ["InboxDollars", "ORG"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["This Nintendo Switch", "PERSON"], ["Jolly Rancher", "PERSON"], ["https://www.uber.com/us/en/s/c/deliver/?invite_code=ztsjjwsrz", "PERSON"], ["Halloween Balloons", "ORG"], ["Gift BasketPrize", "PERSON"], ["Uber Eats", "PERSON"], ["Hairy Spider Props", "PERSON"], ["Remote Timer", "ORG"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"], ["Easter, Mother's", "ORG"], ["Fine Milk", "PERSON"], ["Christa Sunderland", "PERSON"], ["NSFW", "ORG"], ["obese", "NORP"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Piece )", "ORG"], ["five", "CARDINAL"], ["Day Assortment", "ORG"], ["Luckyland Slots - $", "PERSON"], ["The UK England The Very Best", "ORG"], ["Canadian", "NORP"], ["PayPal", "ORG"], ["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Cadbury Dairy", "PERSON"], ["Lantern String Lights", "PERSON"], ["Twitch", "PERSON"], ["Ill", "GPE"], ["Bloody Tablecover", "ORG"], ["eGift CardsNo", "PERSON"], ["Cosplay - Unique Designs for Boys & Girls", "PERSON"], ["Aloe Vera", "ORG"], ["Second", "MONEY"], ["REESE'S Assorted Milk Chocolate Candy Variety Box", "ORG"], ["Party Mix -  Pounds", "PERSON"], ["Jack", "PERSON"], ["Mixed Bag", "PERSON"], ["kinda", "GPE"], ["DSLR", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["Wal-Mart", "ORG"], ["BlackOGWAI Halloween Projector Lights Outdoor Decorations", "ORG"], ["Cowboy Costume", "PERSON"], ["Candy - Candy Bulk", "PERSON"], ["Fansly", "ORG"], ["Snowman Celebration Chocolate", "PERSON"], ["Jumbo Yarn", "PERSON"], ["Cotton Candy", "PERSON"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["Winner", "PERSON"], ["KIT KAT", "ORG"], ["TrilogyAll", "ORG"], ["Morphsuits Zalgo Costume Kids, The Rake Costume Kids, Monster Costume Kids, Scary Halloween Costumes for BoysDisguise Toddler Blippi CostumeSicypoty Kids Skeleton Costume Glow in the Dark Halloween Costume for Boys BlackMorph Dragon Costume Kids", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Hologram Decor", "PERSON"], ["Dominant", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Treat Candy", "PERSON"], ["SKITTLES Original", "PERSON"], ["Cashback", "PERSON"], ["Swiffer", "NORP"], ["Starbucks", "ORG"], ["Strawberry Dream Doughnut", "PERSON"], ["Candy Apple Green", "ORG"], ["Yard Sign", "PERSON"], ["The Giveaway", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["MyPoints", "ORG"], ["Sour Candy", "PERSON"], ["Lindt Bear & Friends Advent Calendar", "ORG"], ["Love Hersheys Doughnuts", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["https://ko-fi.com/s/f Q  -", "PERSON"], ["Tootsie Rolls", "PERSON"], ["The Tome of SyyxMake", "ORG"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Inflatable Costume", "PERSON"], ["the Cozy Mystery Tribe", "ORG"], ["Nicole Rhodes", "PERSON"], ["Bank Of America", "ORG"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["Birthday Cake - This", "PERSON"], ["Air Heads", "ORG"], ["Nintendo Switch", "PERSON"], ["EOS", "ORG"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["DSRL", "ORG"], ["E. Feist", "PERSON"], ["Costumes Cloak", "PERSON"], ["Lollipops, Lifesavers", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["InchNaughty", "ORG"], ["Spiderman", "PERSON"], ["OnlyFans", "NORP"], ["Candy Bulk - Variety Parade Candies - Pinata Candies - Individually Wrapped", "PERSON"], ["#", "CARDINAL"], ["Modes Lighted Decor", "PERSON"], ["Haunted House Holiday Party Supplies -  PCSJOYIN  Ft", "ORG"], ["Handmade Pumpkin", "PERSON"], ["Join Robinhood", "PERSON"], ["Honey Cake Cookie: Tasty", "PERSON"], ["Cheerleader Costume", "PERSON"], ["Papa", "PERSON"], ["BingoPort", "ORG"], ["Classic Snow", "PERSON"], ["OnlyFans - $", "ORG"], ["We're", "PERSON"], ["Rs", "PRODUCT"], ["videomaker.com", "ORG"], ["Assorted Milk Chocolate", "ORG"], ["Nerds", "GPE"], ["Candy Bulk", "PERSON"], ["Walmart", "ORG"], ["Mens Costume", "PERSON"], ["ten", "CARDINAL"], ["Gift Card - Giveaway -  ", "PERSON"], ["strawberry", "PERSON"], ["Candy - Bulk", "PERSON"], ["GirlsChild Royal Vampire", "ORG"], ["Barnes", "PERSON"], ["Main Prize Category -First Place:  Oval Chevron Embossed Metal Sign", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Scarf", "ORG"], ["Samsung Health", "ORG"], ["Valentines Day", "LOC"], ["Stream Raiders", "ORG"], ["Mandalorian", "NORP"], ["EarringsLuucio Girls Police Officer Costume for Kids", "ORG"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"], ["British", "NORP"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Headwear Cartoon Game Outfit for - Years", "EVENT"], ["YouTube", "ORG"], ["Wormate.io", "ORG"], ["Black Friday", "EVENT"], ["Gibson Custom Les", "PERSON"], ["Straight Talk", "PERSON"], ["Hairy Spider", "PERSON"], ["Crumble Cookies", "ORG"], ["The Hobbit & The Lord of the Rings", "ORG"], ["CHRISTA", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["SocialToaster Advocate", "ORG"], ["fourth", "ORDINAL"], ["BingoPort Bulletin", "FAC"], ["Halloween Yard Decorations Party", "ORG"], ["Tik Tok", "PERSON"], ["Twitter", "PERSON"], ["Brownie Batter", "PRODUCT"], ["Tasty", "PERSON"], ["Banner", "ORG"], ["Armor Adult CostumeSATINIOR", "ORG"], ["Role Play Kit", "PERSON"], ["Kreme", "PERSON"], ["Robinhood", "PRODUCT"], ["Different Slides for Different Festivals - Halloween", "ORG"], ["the Les Paul", "ORG"], ["Swedish", "NORP"], ["Eastern Standard Time", "LOC"], ["Gibson Custom Les Paul  Reissue VOS", "PERSON"], ["Slip", "PERSON"], ["Dollar Tree", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["USA", "GPE"], ["Giant Mix - Pinata", "PERSON"], ["Modes Waterproof Battery", "ORG"], ["Double Chocolate  Chip", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corp.", "PERSON"], ["Lantern, Ghost & Witch", "ORG"], ["Honey Cake Cookie", "PERSON"], ["Rosie", "PERSON"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["New Year Day", "EVENT"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["Dunkin' Donuts", "ORG"], ["Individually Wrapped Trick", "PERSON"], ["Peanut Butter  Cup", "PERSON"], ["Role Play - Perfect Dress-", "PERSON"], ["Valentine", "PERSON"], ["Sour Patch", "PERSON"], ["GPT", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Giveaway Details", "PERSON"], ["Port Points", "ORG"], ["Tombstone Hot & Cold", "ORG"], ["Don't", "CARDINAL"], ["Air Costume for", "ORG"], ["Amazon - $", "ORG"], ["Caramel Flavors Miniatures", "ORG"], ["subspace?\"Broadly", "ORDINAL"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Creations Adult", "PERSON"], ["Trade Guitars", "ORG"], ["Giant Spiderweb, Waterproof Battery Operated", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Carawlers", "PERSON"], ["UserTesting - $", "ORG"], ["Hanging Swirl", "ORG"], ["Holiday Decorations", "ORG"], ["Haribo Gold-Bears Gummi", "PERSON"], ["Caramel Shortbread", "PERSON"], ["NC", "GPE"], ["Sided Superhero Capes & Costumes Set for Kids - Ideal", "ORG"], ["ShezGotYarn", "ORG"], ["Birthday Cake", "PERSON"], ["Mask Skeleton Gloves Set", "PERSON"], ["SocialToaster", "ORG"], ["St. Patrick's", "GPE"], ["Shopkick", "PERSON"], ["Gift BasketBy", "PERSON"], ["KREMETM", "ORG"], ["Houseman", "PERSON"], ["Reese", "NORP"], ["Skeleton Skull Lighted Holiday Displays", "PERSON"], ["DMV", "ORG"], ["Newspaper  Stripe", "PERSON"], ["Straight Talk", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["KissMyCash", "GPE"], ["Join Evidation", "PERSON"], ["Bank Of America - $", "ORG"], ["Best Halloween Outdoor DecorationsJOYIN  Pack Halloween Party Decoration", "ORG"], ["Uber Eats - $", "PERSON"], ["Papa", "ORG"], ["Large Spider", "PERSON"], ["Cover Festive Party Supplies", "ORG"], ["Super Stretch Cobwebs", "ORG"], ["US", "GPE"], ["Props Outdoor Decor for", "ORG"], ["subspace", "ORG"], ["Adult", "PERSON"], ["RF mount", "PRODUCT"], ["Brian Croxford", "PERSON"], ["them?Cotton Candy - Pretty", "FAC"], ["Pounds - Assorted", "PERSON"], ["Robinhood", "FAC"], ["Telephia - $", "ORG"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Peanut Butter Cookie", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks - $", "LAW"], ["Hershey Assorted Flavored Miniatures", "ORG"], ["Tetris", "PRODUCT"], ["EF", "ORG"], ["Fantasy Books Bundle", "PERSON"], ["Candy Filled", "PERSON"], ["Epic Book Series", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Sweepstakes", "PERSON"], ["Honeygain", "GPE"], ["megapixel stills", "ORG"], ["Advent Calendar", "PERSON"], ["Thanksgiving Day", "EVENT"], ["Caramel Shortbread - This cookie", "PERSON"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["Sour Punch", "PERSON"], ["Hey Boo Autumn Table Centerpiece", "ORG"], ["White Chocolates", "ORG"], ["Rebel Rouge Labs", "ORG"], ["KREMETM Doughnut", "PERSON"], ["Skittles", "PERSON"], ["https://www.twitch.tv/breakmydreams Yayness", "PERSON"], ["IG", "ORG"], ["Halloween Flameless LED Floating Candles", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Q  - $", "PERSON"], ["Jumpsuit Costume", "PERSON"], ["Candy Bulk Bag", "PERSON"], ["J. Wurts & Feist: Empire", "ORG"], ["Golden Hearts Games - $", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Seated", "ORG"], [": Color The Cover - Composition Notebook", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["SKITTLES Wild Berry", "PERSON"], ["Cop Costume Role Play Kit", "PERSON"]], "lemmas": ["check", "new", "book", "author", "find", "enjoyable", "podcast", "think", "actually", "follow", "disciplined", "dream", "job", "instead", "slack", "go", "awhile", "actually", "worth", "live", "longterm", "stop", "slack", "go", "stay", "disciplined", "kidney", "stone", "find", "yesterday", "bit", "pain", "nauseate", "honestly", "get", "deal", "kidney", "stone", "surprise", "anymore", "live", "tell", "doctor", "immediately", "see", "dehydrate", "honestly", "stay", "hydrated", "surprising", "dehydrate", "news", "get", "huge", "wake", "go", "work", "change", "thing", "avoid", "get", "bad", "honestly", "want", "health", "scare", "go", "easy", "change", "need", "necessary", "call", "overweight", "fan", "hear", "bring", "memory", "bully", "elementary", "school", "young", "hurt", "morning", "deal", "earache", "hope", "go", "away", "soon", "bad", "job", "look", "require", "experience", "pay", "wrong", "love", "housekeeping", "favorite", "cashier", "stocking", "favorite", "far", "housekeeping", "pay", "hourly", "housekeeper", "look", "new", "job", "experience", "pay", "experience", "need", "job", "time", "time", "end", "meet", "time", "time", "job", "actually", "hour", "time", "work", "pay", "love", "job", "get", "overtime", "trouble", "job", "hunting", "work", "content", "creator", "online", "work", "craft", "mystery", "shopping", "livestreame", "job", "time", "actually", "pay", "live", "hey", "check", "app", "earn", "money", "meal", "use", "link", "sign", "ll", "bonus", "meal", "kinda", "pickle", "work", "feel", "like", "go", "lose", "job", "base", "stocking", "manager", "tell", "go", "start", "stocker", "go", "start", "write", "stock", "box", "hour", "normal", "stocking", "day", "write", "up", "thing", "correct", "uboat", "pallet", "truck", "day", "base", "say", "yesterday", "likely", "write", "uboat", "box", "mean", "take", "half", "hour", "complete", "take", "entire", "shift", "mean", "super", "thin", "ice", "work", "previous", "write", "up", "go", "lose", "job", "write", "stock", "box", "fast", "let", "overthinke", "position", "post", "reddit", "page", "ask", "number", "report", "violation", "annousmously", "store", "manager", "see", "ask", "end", "tell", "feel", "like", "violation", "text", "tell", "get", "number", "case", "confident", "call", "say", "want", "mention", "want", "come", "wait", "mention", "stocking", "manager", "say", "feel", "like", "go", "lose", "job", "write", "want", "happen", "reply", "fair", "yesterday", "mention", "want", "truck", "day", "instead", "mean", "chance", "lose", "job", "write", "stock", "box", "hour", "hate", "need", "hour", "week", "work", "hour", "work", "actually", "bring", "money", "pay", "bill", "save", "money", "go", "lose", "lose", "job", "write", "hour", "week", "mention", "like", "well", "training", "know", "box", "hour", "stock", "hour", "feel", "comfortable", "stocking", "worry", "write", "lose", "job", "love", "stocking", "job", "want", "continue", "work", "stocking", "actually", "like", "work", "particuallary", "store", "work", "employee", "costumer", "know", "come", "time", "sigh", "stress", "feel", "like", "go", "fire", "vacation", "day", "lucky", "lose", "job", "lose", "hour", "hour", "holiday", "go", "upset", "need", "hour", "week", "hour", "week", "amazing", "past", "month", "anyways", "need", "finish", "get", "ready", "work", "morning", "need", "stress", "cry", "super", "crappy", "week", "general", "kinda", "quiet", "hide", "avoid", "people", "afraid", "step", "find", "well", "job", "afraid", "lose", "currently", "afraid", "find", "new", "job", "like", "lose", "jobless", "afraid", "position", "kinda", "comfortable", "current", "job", "hour", "time", "work", "realize", "lose", "lose", "current", "job", "new", "job", "work", "lose", "work", "convince", "step", "find", "job", "pay", "time", "experience", "worth", "recent", "cashout", "cash", "reward", "alot", "gift", "card", "choice", "fan", "need", "current", "time", "earn", "survey", "video", "promo", "code", "game", "offer", "member", "like", "join", "head", "link", "today", "join", "need", "help", "join", "let", "know", "share", "earn", "recently", "lifetime", "earning", "remind", "play", "fruit", "play", "head", "think", "play", "game", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "cashout", "gift", "card", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "promo", "code", "search", "web", "complete", "offer", "lot", "reward", "gift", "card", "choose", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "earn", "online", "time", "job", "site", "defiantly", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "cashout", "reward", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "lot", "reward", "choose", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "earn", "online", "time", "job", "site", "definitely", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "know", "count", "get", "close", "know", "love", "love", "have", "advent", "calendar", "countdown", "want", "share", "one", "find", "hope", "enjoy", "let", "know", "oz", "gram", "import", "fill", "day", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "app", "year", "believe", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earning", "site", "use", "money", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "payment", "method", "choose", "image", "mind", "love", "use", "alot", "awhile", "cashout", "wait", "awhile", "cash", "app", "let", "run", "background", "device", "check", "app", "free", "point", "daily", "honey", "jar", "cashout", "will", "love", "app", "let", "run", "money", "show", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "love", "app", "year", "earn", "reward", "mainly", "cashout", "gift", "card", "gift", "card", "one", "tempt", "day", "cash", "reward", "today", "app", "unlock", "phone", "occasionally", "watch", "video", "earn", "point", "download", "app", "play", "game", "earn", "extra", "point", "like", "earn", "reward", "unlock", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "start", "earn", "reward", "sigh", "comment", "early", "think", "ex", "boyfriend", "sure", "want", "cry", "feeling", "ex", "boyfriend", "wish", "able", "friend", "cut", "life", "way", "leave", "comment", "think", "sigh", "leave", "wrong", "way", "wish", "leave", "correct", "way", "hurt", "badly", "learn", "relationship", "thing", "guy", "fair", "happen", "sigh", "ex", "boyfriend", "good", "guy", "perfect", "grow", "alot", "leave", "grow", "grow", "leave", "time", "life", "need", "learn", "adult", "independent", "thank", "bad", "part", "life", "pass", "away", "yeah", "keep", "alive", "cat", "wish", "leave", "living", "stable", "fair", "sigh", "yeah", "go", "kinda", "leave", "need", "sigh", "hope", "mood", "headspace", "memory", "ex", "boyfriend", "mess", "honestly", "stress", "feel", "like", "fail", "live", "go", "lose", "work", "thing", "change", "job", "wise", "continue", "independent", "responsible", "adult", "choice", "feel", "like", "struggle", "hate", "will", "help", "take", "step", "new", "job", "sigh", "memory", "suck", "relationship", "suck", "adult", "suck", "emotion", "suck", "come", "big", "night", "need", "decoration", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "outdoor", "decoration", "hand", "time", "pc", "lead", "led", "operate", "color", "change", "operate", "led", "x", "include", "decoration", "d", "decorationsfunpeny", "o", "lantern", "x", "inchvanthylit", "lead", "operate", "lead", "centerpiece", "fall", "note", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "pay", "healthy", "connect", "app", "start", "earn", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "example", "app", "connect", "earn", "point", "connect", "app", "connect", "use", "earn", "total", "app", "late", "cashout", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "today", "reward", "option", "count", "redemption", "reward", "reward", "come", "big", "night", "need", "decoration", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "outdoor", "decoration", "hand", "time", "outdoor", "decorationsjoyin", "hang", "ghost", "cute", "sqft", "lead", "decoration", "decoration", "beware", "scary", "web", "led", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "follow", "subscribe", "subscribe", "sub", "live", "stream", "like", "song", "request", "direct", "message", "comment", "response", "shoutout", "scene", "video", "cost", "month", "subscribe", "hope", "soon", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "hand", "time", "s", "woman", "s", "s", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "link", "pick", "free", "stock", "order", "free", "stock", "set", "account", "link", "bank", "account", "stock", "range", "lead", "company", "stock", "join", "invest", "alot", "stock", "choose", "perform", "let", "know", "know", "stock", "market", "work", "learn", "pick", "stock", "see", "family", "member", "stock", "wise", "perform", "time", "work", "favor", "far", "stock", "different", "one", "cash", "work", "build", "stock", "have", "helpful", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "hand", "time", "trick", "appeal", "s", "s", "costume", "fit", "adult", "note", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "hi", "think", "love", "free", "app", "reward", "shopping", "brand", "love", "visit", "store", "sign", "code", "bonus", "kick", "use", "code", "EASY", "cash", "reward", "time", "start", "app", "reward", "shopping", "store", "online", "use", "earn", "reward", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "hand", "time", "girl", "costumetchh", "kid", "yearsamobon", "kid", "lead", "light", "girl", "lead", "light", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "hand", "time", "scary", "led", "kid", "double", "kid", "inflatable", "girl", "color", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "come", "big", "night", "candy", "trick", "treater", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "candy", "hand", "time", "give", "trick", "treater", "fish", "lb", "individually", "wrap", "kid", "treat", "individually", "ct", "o", "individually", "wrap", "treat", "individually", "include", "later", "individually", "wrap", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "come", "big", "night", "candy", "trick", "treater", "think", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "candy", "hand", "time", "give", "trick", "treater", "oz", "oz", "oz", "oz", "oz", "ozhershey", "oz", "oz", "oz", "note", "link", "post", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "cost", "extra", "qualifying", "purchase", "receive", "small", "commension", "sure", "actual", "video", "comment", "enter", "win", "giveaway", "good", "luck", "win", "come", "let", "know", "comment", "subscribe", "channelfollow", "alliedawson", "like", "videoleave", "comment", "reach", "extra", "entry", "follow", "try", "site", "today", "start", "site", "normal", "use", "link", "instead", "site", "work", "little", "bit", "site", "work", "secret", "make", "money", "site", "star", "people", "wait", "till", "message", "pay", "conversation", "earn", "site", "refer", "new", "people", "have", "sign", "link", "turn", "give", "start", "site", "try", "free", "drink", "friend", "turn", "spend", "real", "money", "free", "drink", "order", "qualify", "earn", "free", "drink", "friend", "join", "qualifying", "pay", "promote", "profile", "help", "well", "ranking", "help", "earn", "money", "site", "personally", "see", "earn", "pay", "promote", "profile", "right", "note", "referral", "link", "post", "receive", "small", "incentive", "use", "subscribe", "leave", "comment", "video", "head", "giveaway", "form", "enter", "win", "bar", "soap", "giveaway", "end", "app", "year", "believe", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earning", "site", "use", "money", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "right", "currently", "work", "time", "job", "close", "quitting", "post", "currently", "open", "availability", "seriously", "need", "time", "job", "pick", "free", "hour", "total", "hour", "week", "different", "distract", "look", "see", "get", "time", "job", "know", "good", "way", "day", "work", "job", "split", "day", "job", "find", "time", "job", "assume", "find", "time", "job", "deal", "time", "job", "time", "job", "income", "little", "work", "tired", "make", "money", "have", "stay", "hour", "week", "work", "store", "need", "money", "come", "pay", "bill", "need", "like", "get", "mope", "fix", "get", "new", "phone", "pay", "friend", "owe", "money", "build", "saving", "etc", "giveaway", "rule", "leave", "comment", "pick", "winner", "winner", "day", "day", "draw", "claim", "prize", "year", "old", "enter", "giveaway", "need", "email", "asap", "need", "address", "phone", "number", "claim", "prize", "package", "mail", "email", "tracking", "numberonce", "package", "mail", "responsible", "package", "thank", "participate", "crochet", "tenstitchblanket", "start", "vacation", "ball", "color", "get", "try", "week", "love", "cookie", "decide", "favorite", "favorite", "try", "honestly", "want", "spot", "week", "app", "year", "believe", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earning", "site", "use", "money", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "app", "year", "believe", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earning", "site", "use", "money", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "open", "year", "start", "draw", "winner", "m", "solely", "responsible", "giveaway", "affiliate", "love", "like", "subscribe", "check", "link", "post", "great", "need", "comment", "ask", "comment", "order", "enter", "use", "random", "comment", "picker", "pick", "winner", "review", "cookie", "week", "want", "start", "say", "picture", "get", "get", "picture", "get", "home", "get", "little", "bit", "melt", "way", "home", "f", "jump", "box", "drive", "home", "moped", "good", "want", "thank", "good", "friend", "sister", "get", "try", "know", "mystery", "cookie", "review", "ranking", "cookie", "cookie", "cute", "sprinkle", "cookie", "love", "look", "graham", "definitely", "wrong", "chocolate", "cookie", "fact", "look", "like", "chocolate", "cupcake", "sell", "store", "make", "cute", "wrong", "peanut", "butter", "cookie", "snicker", "definitely", "ranking", "cookie", "mystery", "cookie", "cookie", "look", "like", "get", "home", "picture", "get", "cookie", "friend", "tell", "get", "love", "review", "video", "review", "able", "good", "thing", "post", "review", "think", "picture", "able", "time", "hope", "enjoy", "feel", "free", "leave", "thought", "comment", "try", "yummy", "cookie", "get", "come", "review", "name", "try", "cookie", "think", "cookie", "prefer", "chocolate", "cookie", "prefer", "topping", "cookie", "thumb", "good", "lucke", "cookie", "cookie", "taste", "great", "topping", "cookie", "thumb", "favorite", "topping", "cookie", "cookie", "thumb", "look", "good", "taste", "good", "cookie", "thumb", "rate", "order", "like", "instead", "thumb", "following", "honestly", "tie", "place", "opinion", "place", "yesterday", "big", "accomplishment", "drive", "work", "rain", "little", "bit", "wind", "ish", "wind", "constant", "help", "alot", "wind", "speed", "constant", "try", "avoid", "drive", "like", "rain", "yesterday", "avoid", "yesterday", "actually", "drive", "deal", "time", "puddle", "suck", "wheel", "avoid", "notice", "wheel", "slip", "drive", "bit", "slow", "attempt", "wear", "new", "rain", "poncho", "get", "work", "blow", "wind", "make", "block", "view", "mirror", "feel", "safe", "put", "deal", "rain", "stop", "take", "mention", "pretty", "soak", "good", "bit", "point", "think", "alot", "encouragement", "friend", "avoid", "remind", "drive", "thing", "like", "daily", "moped", "spend", "drive", "mean", "money", "waste", "point", "try", "well", "experience", "confidence", "drive", "rain", "like", "yesterday", "wind", "drive", "general", "help", "experience", "confidence", "short", "video", "rain", "yesterday", "well", "understanding", "drive", "numb", "try", "process", "loss", "yesterday", "try", "deal", "mom", "pass", "pass", "away", "kinda", "lose", "have", "trouble", "deal", "right", "hit", "mom", "early", "week", "loss", "yesterday", "make", "deal", "mom", "pass", "hard", "year", "easy", "post", "right", "get", "news", "amazing", "picture", "birthday", "memory", "video", "pass", "away", "evening", "month", "th", "wife", "year", "good", "know", "love", "miss", "soon", "get", "week", "stress", "worry", "fill", "paper", "work", "work", "uber", "eat", "nice", "weather", "check", "moped", "hear", "morning", "love", "mope", "find", "time", "job", "time", "job", "place", "thing", "go", "burner", "try", "stress", "need", "money", "come", "currently", "wrong", "give", "hour", "lately", "consistent", "cover", "basis", "find", "work", "well", "busy", "week", "week", "hope", "need", "think", "today", "stocking", "yarn", "thing", "like", "get", "yesterday", "evening", "way", "home", "work", "hour", "having", "hour", "sleep", "day", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "wish", "talk", "use", "advice", "situation", "currently", "know", "right", "thing", "ready", "scared", "lose", "safety", "net", "have", "thing", "work", "postpone", "need", "situation", "prove", "ok", "lose", "safety", "net", "played", "new", "game", "honestly", "love", "somewhat", "addicted", "livestreame", "ride", "work", "morning", "bad", "goal", "well", "month", "earning", "actually", "alot", "well", "month", "happy", "hope", "continue", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "pay", "paypal", "instantly", "site", "play", "instant", "win", "game", "slot", "game", "daily", "login", "bonus", "hour", "onlyfan", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spanking", "model", "work", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "want", "post", "reward", "straight", "talk", "costumer", "think", "straight", "talk", "costumer", "soon", "member", "feel", "free", "sign", "join", "straight", "talk", "enroll", "referral", "code", "free", "month", "service", "sign", "today", "feel", "like", "people", "costumer", "forget", "reward", "page", "win", "point", "add", "account", "free", "monthly", "minute", "short", "money", "month", "month", "want", "phone", "bill", "money", "bill", "fun", "spin", "prize", "avaliable", "wheel", "currently", "play", "hour", "win", "morning", "play", "free", "perk", "local", "discount", "choose", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "account", "different", "way", "redeem", "point", "account", "favorite", "use", "free", "service", "plan", "month", "short", "money", "phone", "help", "reward", "goal", "set", "progress", "far", "time", "play", "game", "time", "play", "laptop", "well", "ranking", "far", "game", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "deliver", "delivery", "photo", "work", "today", "nice", "outside", "today", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "pay", "paypal", "instantly", "app", "blogge", "free", "app", "get", "cash", "gas", "use", "promo", "code", "extra", "gal", "bonus", "purchase", "reason", "save", "car", "moped", "cost", "alot", "fill", "fill", "gas", "tank", "complain", "add", "use", "cashback", "add", "bank", "account", "awesome", "reward", "choose", "look", "wash", "look", "dish", "come", "right", "place", "right", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "pay", "paypal", "instantly", "app", "blogge", "look", "soap", "saver", "need", "quick", "easy", "gift", "come", "right", "place", "right", "exciting", "day", "yesterday", "customer", "think", "give", "bill", "owe", "give", "manager", "audit", "verify", "correct", "lady", "go", "owe", "wrong", "want", "number", "regional", "manager", "complain", "today", "talk", "kidney", "stone", "cashout", "reward", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "lot", "reward", "choose", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "earn", "online", "time", "job", "site", "definitely", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "goal", "want", "reach", "channel", "year", "reach", "follower", "captain", "currently", "follower", "away", "goal", "reach", "need", "reach", "average", "viewer", "late", "cashout", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "today", "reward", "option", "count", "redemption", "reward", "reward", "let", "walk", "breakmydreamswatch", "stream", "game", "craft", "outdoor", "activity", "want", "moment", "late", "crochet", "project", "finish", "make", "yesterday", "love", "try", "plan", "soon", "want", "well", "job", "cleaning", "last", "long", "one", "buy", "save", "money", "long", "run", "have", "couple", "one", "reusable", "swiffer", "mop", "video", "show", "head", "watch", "video", "use", "today", "daily", "login", "bonus", "hour", "currently", "wait", "nd", "tomorrow", "morning", "like", "let", "bonus", "log", "save", "start", "play", "game", "game", "tend", "well", "instant", "win", "game", "stick", "sweep", "money", "cashout", "redeem", "send", "bank", "account", "cash", "time", "sure", "right", "hand", "guess", "time", "excited", "year", "fully", "track", "online", "earning", "head", "post", "year", "bad", "start", "year", "want", "well", "earning", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "mainly", "earn", "unlock", "phone", "watch", "video", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "earn", "deliver", "food", "costumer", "bike", "regular", "electric", "scooter", "walk", "earn", "complete", "offer", "survey", "video", "promo", "code", "contest", "app", "year", "believe", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earning", "site", "use", "money", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "pay", "paypal", "instantly", "app", "blogge", "power", "work", "try", "help", "power", "family", "member", "donate", "share", "case", "know", "donate", "help", "donation", "receive", "apricate", "disclaimer", "available", "shop", "drive", "online", "pickup", "delivery", "participate", "shop", "subject", "product", "availability", "offer", "available", "select", "grocery", "store", "supply", "visit", "find", "close", "participate", "location", "unglazed", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "dip", "flavor", "ice", "cover", "semi", "sweet", "chip", "heart", "sprinkle", "chocolate", "ice", "drizzle", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "milk", "chocolate", "filling", "dip", "chocolate", "icing", "cover", "mini", "milk", "chocolate", "pick", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "dip", "chocolate", "icing", "decorate", "buttercream", "ice", "rise", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "strawberry", "flavor", "dip", "red", "icing", "cover", "white", "chip", "heart", "sprinkle", "blend", "heart", "shape", "fill", "doughnut", "dip", "red", "icing", "decorate", "sprinkle", "doughnut", "available", "available", "select", "grocery", "store", "select", "convenience", "store", "end", "dip", "ice", "top", "sprinkle", "blend", "end", "enter", "today", "end", "prize", "award", "x", "value", "place", "value", "x", "value", "category", "purchase", "necessary", "enter", "win", "resident", "exclude", "age", "old", "enter", "prohibit", "law", "official", "detail", "sign", "sign", "today", "enter", "today", "r", "giant", "frame", "mirrorless", "camera", "pack", "punch", "predecessor", "affordable", "price", "tag", "r", "give", "k", "output", "fully", "articulating", "monitor", "heft", "canon", "dslr", "internally", "capture", "video", "feature", "canon", "industry", "lead", "dual", "pixel", "autofocus", "pair", "camera", "innovative", "lens", "mount", "adapter", "lense", "brand", "new", "give", "camera", "away", "lucky", "winner", "competition", "open", "worldwide", "forget", "complete", "entry", "bonus", "entry", "not", "access", "competition", "social", "channel", "email", "communication", "will", "not", "select", "winner", "enter", "today", "end", "chance", "win", "skincare", "prize", "purchase", "necessary", "enter", "resident", "year", "age", "old", "enter", "today", "oled", "entry", "win", "awesome", "prize", "complete", "action", "gain", "bonus", "entry", "share", "contest", "detail", "friend", "enter", "qty", "ole", "tee", "shirt", "place", "qty", "carbellion", "tee", "shirt", "sticker", "today", "win", "cozy", "mystery", "bookworm", "basket", "enter", "email", "address", "consent", "receive", "email", "contest", "open", "resident", "find", "sorry", "late", "fall", "online", "earning", "track", "money", "get", "time", "job", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earning", "catch", "earning", "post", "sure", "goal", "earning", "safe", "let", "earn", "money", "general", "want", "year", "entire", "year", "time", "track", "online", "earning", "proud", "happy", "total", "year", "tell", "go", "work", "improve", "earning", "able", "follow", "journey", "post", "monthly", "blog", "post", "like", "help", "track", "earning", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spanking", "model", "work", "late", "payment", "proof", "site", "earn", "lot", "different", "offer", "survey", "video", "lot", "run", "contest", "month", "daily", "payment", "need", "cash", "earn", "total", "speak", "generally", "regard", "moderate", "deep", "trace", "like", "condition", "experience", "submissive", "intense", "erotic", "interaction", "subspace", "deep", "go", "subspace", "experience", "subspace", "easily", "hard", "answer", "subspace", "time", "year", "point", "start", "zone", "float", "far", "away", "super", "far", "speak", "anymore", "awhile", "scene", "end", "find", "subspace", "hard", "hate", "love", "subspace", "alot", "personally", "take", "alot", "think", "come", "people", "play", "enter", "subspace", "freak", "reaction", "scene", "having", "change", "stop", "scene", "bring", "let", "enjoy", "subspace", "enjoy", "feel", "like", "sort", "unconscious", "block", "subspace", "want", "play", "experience", "change", "happen", "sub", "enter", "subspace", "freak", "pull", "immediately", "able", "enjoy", "scene", "sub", "enter", "let", "enjoy", "long", "deep", "let", "enjoy", "scene", "hopefully", "enter", "want", "place", "long", "term", "place", "home", "worry", "move", "month", "year", "fun", "stressful", "current", "lease", "end", "end", "birthday", "month", "pretty", "sure", "end", "owner", "talk", "want", "sell", "move", "decide", "roommate", "upstairs", "want", "stay", "year", "college", "wish", "friend", "willing", "apartment", "couple", "year", "feel", "like", "home", "try", "figure", "realistic", "goal", "work", "month", "year", "ready", "lease", "end", "end", "save", "money", "save", "money", "payment", "room", "want", "start", "look", "new", "place", "room", "need", "try", "avoid", "close", "lease", "ending", "have", "place", "till", "minute", "like", "time", "have", "place", "like", "want", "homeless", "close", "homeless", "stressful", "time", "like", "wish", "boyfriend", "help", "expense", "well", "living", "arrangement", "sigh", "honestly", "sure", "want", "boyfriend", "kinda", "like", "single", "guy", "kinda", "complicated", "day", "leftenter", "today", "enter", "chance", "win", "bundle", "popular", "time", "winner", "receive", "series", "include", "include", "saga", "entrance", "receive", "copy", "sure", "download", "link", "send", "emailenter", "free", "egift", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "day", "end", "today", "egift", "card", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "th", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "card", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "card", "end", "today", "egift", "card", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "card", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "card", "today", "enter", "egift", "end", "today", "enter", "egift", "card", "valentine", "today", "today", "help", "play", "grow", "reward", "lucky", "winner", "seriously", "incredible", "away", "play", "reach", "subscriber", "link", "link", "spot", "easy", "fan", "find", "work", "online", "late", "cashout", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "today", "reward", "option", "count", "redemption", "reward", "reward", "officially", "year", "honestly", "good", "thing", "life", "reason", "excited", "year", "dream", "happen", "actually", "happen", "miss", "cat", "hope", "ex", "boyfriend", "excited", "make", "goal", "happen", "able", "thank", "amazing", "good", "friend", "help", "introduce", "amazing", "good", "friend", "life", "think", "live", "amazing", "site", "creator", "want", "join", "try", "success", "well", "success", "like", "check", "content", "head", "link", "today", "page", "note", "page", "content", "right", "join", "get", "accept", "creator", "today", "like", "creator", "head", "link", "today", "join", "like", "learn", "head", "blog", "post", "today", "note", "link", "post", "maybe", "referral", "link", "small", "discount", "money", "join", "use", "make", "content", "work", "get", "set", "quad", "game", "lucky", "catch", "video", "want", "highlight", "remember", "reaction", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "come", "today", "offer", "referral", "link", "play", "couple", "game", "site", "end", "win", "nice", "notice", "complete", "profile", "earn", "free", "daily", "free", "daily", "happen", "premium", "subscriber", "e", "magazine", "unlimited", "supply", "free", "bingo", "session", "site", "day", "week", "hour", "day", "chance", "win", "session", "right", "test", "site", "thank", "earn", "redeem", "reward", "say", "reward", "let", "know", "legit", "fun", "site", "kinda", "kill", "time", "fan", "bingo", "like", "cash", "reward", "today", "app", "unlock", "phone", "occasionally", "watch", "video", "earn", "point", "download", "app", "play", "game", "earn", "extra", "point", "like", "earn", "reward", "unlock", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "start", "earn", "reward", "show", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "love", "app", "year", "earn", "reward", "mainly", "cashout", "gift", "card", "gift", "card", "one", "tempt", "day", "sorry", "late", "fall", "online", "earning", "track", "money", "get", "time", "job", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earning", "catch", "earning", "post", "sure", "goal", "earning", "safe", "let", "earn", "money", "general", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "favorite", "app", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "week", "earn", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "deposit", "sorry", "late", "fall", "online", "earning", "track", "money", "get", "time", "job", "month", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earning", "catch", "earning", "post", "sure", "goal", "earning", "safe", "let", "earn", "money", "general", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "sure", "money", "honest", "earn", "offer", "debit", "card", "q", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "pay", "paypal", "instantly", "deliever", "bike", "electric", "scooter", "walk", "life", "matter", "bad", "hurt", "love", "work", "good", "way", "know", "year", "career", "personal", "record", "date", "story", "unconditional", "love", "heartbreak", "hi", "think", "love", "free", "app", "reward", "shopping", "brand", "love", "visit", "store", "sign", "code", "bonus", "kick", "use", "code", "EASY", "cash", "reward", "time", "start", "app", "reward", "shopping", "store", "online", "use", "earn", "reward", "explain", "change", "requirement", "state", "city", "live", "mind", "scooter", "sigh", "feel", "like", "able", "mope", "option", "deliver", "able", "actually", "money", "mess", "bike", "walk", "couple", "year", "sigh", "start", "link", "passive", "income", "app", "phone", "computer", "work", "cashout", "new", "youtube", "video", "review", "water", "sorry", "late", "fall", "online", "earning", "track", "money", "get", "time", "job", "month", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earning", "catch", "earning", "post", "goal", "earning", "well", "goal", "earning", "earning", "earn", "online", "site", "app", "let", "know", "far", "year", "site", "let", "choose", "charity", "support", "choose", "cashout", "earning", "gift", "card", "paypal", "direct", "deposit", "option", "change", "earning", "coin", "survey", "site", "survey", "computer", "cell", "phone", "pay", "hit", "task", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spanking", "model", "work", "sure", "money", "honest", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "instal", "app", "know", "post", "sure", "great", "year", "up", "down", "feel", "like", "up", "down", "way", "end", "scared", "hurt", "upset", "unsure", "go", "lose", "confuse", "right", "want", "end", "lose", "currently", "love", "live", "right", "close", "downtown", "good", "neighborhood", "tell", "want", "homeless", "honesty", "happen", "live", "time", "happen", "end", "cause", "breakdown", "scare", "good", "friend", "cause", "issue", "friend", "happen", "time", "year", "middle", "birthday", "get", "lucky", "find", "place", "homeless", "currently", "deal", "scare", "take", "away", "big", "chunk", "income", "come", "work", "time", "hour", "time", "manager", "sort", "pay", "manager", "sort", "bring", "need", "mean", "month", "bring", "pay", "bill", "rent", "good", "leave", "buy", "grocery", "need", "buy", "month", "money", "gas", "moped", "fill", "money", "saving", "money", "stock", "friend", "karoke", "poker", "currently", "cost", "play", "etc", "eat", "friend", "awhile", "able", "vacation", "want", "away", "bit", "try", "think", "stay", "positive", "thing", "go", "end", "work", "money", "situation", "normal", "well", "end", "bill", "will", "pay", "scary", "thing", "will", "money", "pay", "rent", "post", "thing", "come", "time", "kinda", "need", "head", "kinda", "look", "future", "go", "overall", "go", "jump", "run", "errand", "procrastinate", "month", "moped", "get", "oil", "change", "fair", "sick", "bit", "struggle", "afraid", "drive", "day", "week", "traffic", "road", "afraid", "drive", "night", "traffic", "deal", "want", "drive", "think", "play", "huge", "role", "struggle", "drive", "go", "work", "year", "go", "work", "get", "driver", "license", "point", "year", "get", "video", "hope", "enjoy", "let", "know", "like", "get", "let", "know", "get", "couple", "goal", "want", "work", "year", "work", "drive", "moped", "want", "sit", "waste", "money", "spend", "want", "need", "driving", "experience", "general", "need", "work", "drive", "new", "area", "see", "like", "road", "big", "fan", "need", "work", "feel", "well", "road", "mess", "work", "get", "time", "job", "pay", "find", "time", "job", "pay", "well", "slack", "etc", "build", "saving", "stock", "want", "money", "future", "emergency", "etc", "break", "lose", "progress", "move", "live", "get", "driving", "experience", "car", "license", "get", "place", "rent", "room", "actually", "space", "miss", "actually", "have", "place", "actually", "home", "actually", "feel", "like", "home", "work", "get", "weight", "health", "good", "place", "energy", "feel", "happy", "slack", "need", "stop", "one", "think", "right", "work", "currently", "year", "past", "want", "work", "general", "want", "life"], "pos": [["Check", "VERB"], ["newest", "ADJ"], ["book", "NOUN"], ["Author", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["enjoyable", "ADJ"], ["podcast", "NOUN"], ["thinking", "VERB"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["follow", "VERB"], ["disciplined", "ADJ"], ["dream", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["instead", "ADV"], ["slacking", "VERB"], ["going", "VERB"], ["awhile", "ADV"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["worth", "ADJ"], ["living", "VERB"], ["longterm", "NOUN"], ["stop", "VERB"], ["slacking", "VERB"], ["going", "VERB"], ["stay", "VERB"], ["disciplined", "ADJ"], ["kidney", "NOUN"], ["stone", "NOUN"], ["found", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["pain", "NOUN"], ["nauseated", "VERB"], ["Honestly", "ADV"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["dealing", "VERB"], ["kidney", "NOUN"], ["stones", "NOUN"], ["surprise", "VERB"], ["anymore", "ADV"], ["live", "VERB"], ["told", "VERB"], ["doctor", "NOUN"], ["immediately", "ADV"], ["seeing", "VERB"], ["dehydrated", "VERB"], ["honestly", "ADV"], ["stay", "VERB"], ["hydrated", "ADJ"], ["surprising", "ADJ"], ["dehydrated", "VERB"], ["news", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["huge", "ADJ"], ["wake", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["working", "VERB"], ["changing", "VERB"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["avoid", "VERB"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["worse", "ADJ"], ["honestly", "ADV"], ["want", "VERB"], ["health", "NOUN"], ["scare", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["easy", "ADJ"], ["change", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["necessary", "ADJ"], ["called", "VERB"], ["overweight", "ADJ"], ["fan", "NOUN"], ["hearing", "VERB"], ["Brings", "VERB"], ["memories", "NOUN"], ["bullied", "VERB"], ["elementary", "ADJ"], ["school", "NOUN"], ["younger", "ADJ"], ["hurts", "VERB"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["dealing", "VERB"], ["earache", "NOUN"], ["hoping", "VERB"], ["goes", "VERB"], ["away", "ADV"], ["soon", "ADV"], ["worse", "ADJ"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["look", "VERB"], ["require", "VERB"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["love", "VERB"], ["housekeeping", "NOUN"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["cashiering", "VERB"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["favorite", "NOUN"], ["far", "ADV"], ["housekeeping", "NOUN"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["hourly", "ADJ"], ["housekeeper", "NOUN"], ["looking", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["need", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["ends", "NOUN"], ["meet", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["work", "VERB"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["love", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["overtime", "NOUN"], ["trouble", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["hunting", "NOUN"], ["working", "VERB"], ["content", "NOUN"], ["creator", "NOUN"], ["online", "ADJ"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["crafting", "VERB"], ["mystery", "NOUN"], ["shopping", "NOUN"], ["livestreaming", "VERB"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["live", "VERB"], ["Hey", "INTJ"], ["check", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["meal", "NOUN"], ["Use", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["ll", "AUX"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["meal", "NOUN"], ["kinda", "ADJ"], ["pickle", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["going", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["based", "VERB"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["manager", "NOUN"], ["told", "VERB"], ["going", "VERB"], ["start", "VERB"], ["stockers", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["start", "VERB"], ["writing", "VERB"], ["stocking", "VERB"], ["boxes", "NOUN"], ["hour", "NOUN"], ["normal", "ADJ"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["write", "VERB"], ["ups", "NOUN"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["correct", "ADJ"], ["uboats", "NOUN"], ["pallets", "NOUN"], ["truck", "NOUN"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["based", "VERB"], ["said", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["likely", "ADV"], ["wrote", "VERB"], ["uboat", "NOUN"], ["boxes", "NOUN"], ["meaning", "VERB"], ["taken", "VERB"], ["half", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["complete", "VERB"], ["took", "VERB"], ["entire", "ADJ"], ["shift", "NOUN"], ["Meaning", "VERB"], ["super", "ADJ"], ["thin", "ADJ"], ["ice", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["previous", "ADJ"], ["write", "ADJ"], ["ups", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["write", "NOUN"], ["stocking", "VERB"], ["boxes", "NOUN"], ["fast", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["overthinking", "VERB"], ["position", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["reddit", "NOUN"], ["page", "NOUN"], ["asking", "VERB"], ["number", "NOUN"], ["report", "VERB"], ["violations", "NOUN"], ["annousmously", "ADV"], ["store", "NOUN"], ["manager", "NOUN"], ["saw", "VERB"], ["asked", "VERB"], ["ended", "VERB"], ["telling", "VERB"], ["felt", "VERB"], ["like", "ADP"], ["violations", "NOUN"], ["text", "NOUN"], ["told", "VERB"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["number", "NOUN"], ["case", "NOUN"], ["confident", "ADJ"], ["called", "VERB"], ["said", "VERB"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["mentioned", "VERB"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["come", "VERB"], ["waiting", "VERB"], ["mention", "VERB"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["manager", "NOUN"], ["said", "VERB"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["going", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["write", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["happen", "VERB"], ["reply", "VERB"], ["fair", "ADJ"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["mention", "VERB"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["truck", "NOUN"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["instead", "ADV"], ["means", "VERB"], ["chance", "NOUN"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["wrote", "VERB"], ["stocking", "VERB"], ["boxes", "NOUN"], ["hour", "NOUN"], ["hate", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["brought", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["bills", "NOUN"], ["save", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["write", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["mentioned", "VERB"], ["like", "VERB"], ["better", "ADJ"], ["training", "NOUN"], ["know", "VERB"], ["boxes", "NOUN"], ["hour", "NOUN"], ["stocking", "VERB"], ["hour", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["comfortable", "ADJ"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["worrying", "VERB"], ["wrote", "VERB"], ["losing", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["continue", "VERB"], ["working", "VERB"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["like", "INTJ"], ["working", "VERB"], ["particuallary", "NOUN"], ["store", "NOUN"], ["working", "VERB"], ["employees", "NOUN"], ["costumers", "NOUN"], ["know", "VERB"], ["come", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["stressing", "VERB"], ["feeling", "VERB"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["going", "VERB"], ["fired", "VERB"], ["vacation", "NOUN"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["lucky", "ADJ"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["holiday", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["upset", "ADJ"], ["need", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["amazing", "ADJ"], ["past", "ADJ"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["Anyways", "ADV"], ["need", "VERB"], ["finish", "VERB"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["ready", "ADJ"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["needed", "VERB"], ["stressing", "VERB"], ["crying", "VERB"], ["super", "ADV"], ["crappy", "ADJ"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["general", "ADJ"], ["kinda", "ADV"], ["quiet", "ADJ"], ["hiding", "VERB"], ["avoiding", "VERB"], ["people", "NOUN"], ["afraid", "ADJ"], ["step", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["better", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["afraid", "ADJ"], ["losing", "VERB"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["afraid", "ADJ"], ["find", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["like", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["jobless", "ADJ"], ["afraid", "ADJ"], ["position", "NOUN"], ["kinda", "ADV"], ["comfortable", "ADJ"], ["current", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["realizing", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["current", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["work", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["worked", "VERB"], ["convince", "VERB"], ["step", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["pays", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["worth", "ADJ"], ["recent", "ADJ"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["cashed", "VERB"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["card", "NOUN"], ["choices", "NOUN"], ["fan", "NOUN"], ["need", "VERB"], ["current", "ADJ"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["codes", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["offers", "NOUN"], ["member", "NOUN"], ["like", "VERB"], ["join", "VERB"], ["head", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["join", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["help", "NOUN"], ["joining", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["share", "VERB"], ["earned", "VERB"], ["recently", "ADV"], ["lifetime", "NOUN"], ["earnings", "NOUN"], ["reminds", "VERB"], ["playing", "VERB"], ["fruits", "NOUN"], ["play", "VERB"], ["heading", "VERB"], ["think", "VERB"], ["played", "VERB"], ["game", "NOUN"], ["watch", "VERB"], ["stream", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["crafts", "NOUN"], ["live", "VERB"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["card", "NOUN"], ["mainly", "ADV"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["codes", "NOUN"], ["searching", "VERB"], ["web", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["offers", "NOUN"], ["lots", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["cards", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["search", "NOUN"], ["making", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["earning", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["defiantly", "ADV"], ["join", "VERB"], ["heading", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["join", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["mainly", "ADV"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["playing", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["discover", "NOUN"], ["items", "NOUN"], ["searching", "VERB"], ["web", "NOUN"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["codes", "NOUN"], ["shopping", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["lots", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["search", "NOUN"], ["making", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["earning", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["definitely", "ADV"], ["join", "VERB"], ["heading", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["join", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["know", "VERB"], ["counting", "VERB"], ["gets", "VERB"], ["closer", "ADJ"], ["know", "VERB"], ["loved", "VERB"], ["love", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["advent", "NOUN"], ["calendar", "NOUN"], ["countdown", "NOUN"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["share", "VERB"], ["ones", "NOUN"], ["found", "VERB"], ["Hope", "VERB"], ["enjoy", "VERB"], ["Let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["oz", "ADP"], ["grams", "NOUN"], ["Imported", "VERB"], ["Filled", "VERB"], ["Days", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["tend", "VERB"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["till", "SCONJ"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["recent", "ADJ"], ["payment", "NOUN"], ["proof", "NOUN"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["end", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["Cashout", "NOUN"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["signed", "VERB"], ["survey", "NOUN"], ["earning", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["payment", "NOUN"], ["method", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["image", "NOUN"], ["mind", "VERB"], ["love", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["awhile", "ADV"], ["Cashout", "NOUN"], ["waited", "VERB"], ["awhile", "ADV"], ["cash", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["background", "NOUN"], ["devices", "NOUN"], ["check", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["daily", "ADV"], ["honey", "NOUN"], ["jar", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["wo", "AUX"], ["love", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["shows", "VERB"], ["different", "ADJ"], ["ways", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["YEARS", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["mainly", "ADV"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["cards", "NOUN"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["cards", "NOUN"], ["ones", "NOUN"], ["tempted", "VERB"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["cashed", "VERB"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["unlock", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["occasionally", "ADV"], ["watch", "VERB"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["download", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["play", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["like", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["unlocking", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["head", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["start", "VERB"], ["earning", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["earlier", "ADV"], ["think", "VERB"], ["ex", "NOUN"], ["boyfriend", "NOUN"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["want", "VERB"], ["cry", "VERB"], ["feelings", "NOUN"], ["ex", "NOUN"], ["boyfriend", "NOUN"], ["wish", "VERB"], ["able", "ADJ"], ["friends", "NOUN"], ["cut", "VERB"], ["life", "NOUN"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["left", "VERB"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["think", "VERB"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["left", "VERB"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["wish", "VERB"], ["leave", "VERB"], ["correct", "ADJ"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["hurt", "VERB"], ["badly", "ADV"], ["learn", "VERB"], ["relationship", "NOUN"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["guy", "NOUN"], ["fair", "ADJ"], ["happening", "VERB"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["ex", "NOUN"], ["boyfriend", "NOUN"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["guy", "NOUN"], ["perfect", "ADJ"], ["grown", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["leaving", "VERB"], ["grew", "VERB"], ["grew", "VERB"], ["leaving", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["life", "NOUN"], ["needed", "VERB"], ["learn", "VERB"], ["adult", "NOUN"], ["independent", "ADJ"], ["thank", "VERB"], ["worst", "ADJ"], ["parts", "NOUN"], ["life", "NOUN"], ["passed", "VERB"], ["away", "ADV"], ["yeah", "INTJ"], ["kept", "VERB"], ["alive", "ADJ"], ["cat", "NOUN"], ["wish", "VERB"], ["left", "VERB"], ["living", "NOUN"], ["stable", "ADJ"], ["fair", "ADJ"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["yeah", "INTJ"], ["going", "VERB"], ["kinda", "ADV"], ["leave", "VERB"], ["needed", "VERB"], ["sighs", "VERB"], ["hoping", "VERB"], ["mood", "NOUN"], ["headspace", "NOUN"], ["memories", "NOUN"], ["ex", "NOUN"], ["boyfriend", "NOUN"], ["messed", "VERB"], ["honestly", "ADV"], ["stressed", "VERB"], ["feeling", "VERB"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["failing", "VERB"], ["living", "VERB"], ["going", "VERB"], ["lose", "VERB"], ["worked", "VERB"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["change", "VERB"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["wise", "ADJ"], ["continuing", "VERB"], ["independent", "ADJ"], ["responsible", "ADJ"], ["adult", "NOUN"], ["choices", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["struggling", "VERB"], ["hate", "VERB"], ["wo", "AUX"], ["help", "VERB"], ["taking", "VERB"], ["step", "NOUN"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["sighs", "NOUN"], ["memories", "NOUN"], ["suck", "VERB"], ["relationships", "NOUN"], ["suck", "VERB"], ["adult", "NOUN"], ["sucks", "NOUN"], ["emotions", "NOUN"], ["suck", "VERB"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["decorations", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["outdoor", "ADJ"], ["decorations", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["pcs", "VERB"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["LEDs", "NOUN"], ["Operated", "VERB"], ["Color", "NOUN"], ["Changing", "VERB"], ["Operated", "VERB"], ["LED", "NOUN"], ["x", "PUNCT"], ["Included", "VERB"], ["Decorations", "NOUN"], ["D", "ADJ"], ["DecorationsFUNPENY", "NOUN"], ["O", "NOUN"], ["Lantern", "NOUN"], ["x", "SYM"], ["inchVanthylit", "ADJ"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["Operated", "VERB"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["Centerpiece", "NOUN"], ["Fall", "VERB"], ["Note", "VERB"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["healthy", "ADJ"], ["connect", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["start", "VERB"], ["earning", "VERB"], ["Head", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["example", "NOUN"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["connect", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["connected", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["connect", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["earned", "VERB"], ["total", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["latest", "ADJ"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["charging", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["listening", "VERB"], ["music", "NOUN"], ["taking", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["installing", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["like", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["head", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["options", "NOUN"], ["Counting", "VERB"], ["redemption", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["decorations", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["outdoor", "ADJ"], ["decorations", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["Outdoor", "AUX"], ["DecorationsJOYIN", "NUM"], ["Hanging", "VERB"], ["Ghosts", "NOUN"], ["Cute", "ADJ"], ["sqft", "NOUN"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["Decorations", "NOUN"], ["Decorations", "NOUN"], ["Beware", "VERB"], ["Scary", "ADJ"], ["Web", "NOUN"], ["LED", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["follow", "VERB"], ["subscribe", "VERB"], ["subscribing", "VERB"], ["sub", "NOUN"], ["live", "ADJ"], ["streams", "NOUN"], ["like", "ADP"], ["song", "NOUN"], ["requests", "NOUN"], ["direct", "ADJ"], ["messages", "NOUN"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["response", "NOUN"], ["shoutout", "NOUN"], ["scenes", "NOUN"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["costs", "VERB"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["subscribe", "VERB"], ["hope", "VERB"], ["soon", "ADV"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["s", "VERB"], ["Women", "NOUN"], ["s", "PART"], ["s", "PART"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["pick", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["stock", "NOUN"], ["order", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["stock", "NOUN"], ["set", "VERB"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["link", "VERB"], ["bank", "NOUN"], ["account", "VERB"], ["stock", "NOUN"], ["range", "NOUN"], ["leading", "VERB"], ["companies", "NOUN"], ["stocks", "NOUN"], ["joined", "VERB"], ["invest", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["stocks", "NOUN"], ["chose", "VERB"], ["performing", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["stock", "NOUN"], ["market", "NOUN"], ["works", "VERB"], ["learning", "VERB"], ["picked", "VERB"], ["stocks", "NOUN"], ["seeing", "VERB"], ["family", "NOUN"], ["members", "NOUN"], ["stock", "NOUN"], ["wise", "ADJ"], ["performing", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["worked", "VERB"], ["favor", "NOUN"], ["far", "ADV"], ["stocks", "NOUN"], ["different", "ADJ"], ["ones", "NOUN"], ["cashed", "VERB"], ["working", "VERB"], ["building", "VERB"], ["stocks", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["helpful", "ADJ"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["Trick", "NOUN"], ["Appealing", "VERB"], ["s", "PART"], ["s", "PART"], ["Costume", "VERB"], ["Fits", "VERB"], ["Adults", "NOUN"], ["Note", "VERB"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["Hi", "INTJ"], ["think", "VERB"], ["love", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "VERB"], ["shopping", "NOUN"], ["brands", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["visiting", "VERB"], ["stores", "NOUN"], ["Sign", "VERB"], ["code", "NOUN"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["kicks", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["code", "NOUN"], ["EASY", "NOUN"], ["cashed", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["times", "NOUN"], ["started", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "VERB"], ["shopping", "NOUN"], ["stores", "NOUN"], ["online", "ADV"], ["use", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["Girls", "NOUN"], ["CostumeTCHH", "NOUN"], ["Kids", "NOUN"], ["YearsAMOBON", "NUM"], ["Kids", "NOUN"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["Light", "NUM"], ["Girls", "NOUN"], ["LED", "VERB"], ["Light", "NUM"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["needing", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["costumes", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["Scary", "ADJ"], ["LED", "NOUN"], ["Kids", "NOUN"], ["Double", "ADJ"], ["Kids", "NOUN"], ["Inflatable", "ADJ"], ["Girls", "NOUN"], ["Colors", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["candy", "NOUN"], ["trick", "NOUN"], ["treaters", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["candy", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["giving", "VERB"], ["trick", "VERB"], ["treaters", "NOUN"], ["Fish", "NOUN"], ["lb", "NUM"], ["Individually", "ADV"], ["Wrapped", "VERB"], ["kid", "NOUN"], ["Treating", "VERB"], ["Individually", "ADV"], ["ct", "ADJ"], ["o", "NOUN"], ["Individually", "ADV"], ["Wrapped", "VERB"], ["Treats", "NOUN"], ["Individually", "ADV"], ["Includes", "VERB"], ["Later", "ADV"], ["Individually", "ADV"], ["Wrapped", "VERB"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["night", "NOUN"], ["candy", "NOUN"], ["trick", "NOUN"], ["treaters", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["finds", "VERB"], ["candy", "NOUN"], ["hands", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["giving", "VERB"], ["trick", "VERB"], ["treaters", "NOUN"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["ozHershey", "PRON"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["oz", "INTJ"], ["Note", "VERB"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["contain", "VERB"], ["affiliate", "NOUN"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["commension", "NOUN"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["actual", "ADJ"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["comment", "VERB"], ["entered", "VERB"], ["win", "VERB"], ["giveaway", "NOUN"], ["Good", "ADJ"], ["luck", "NOUN"], ["win", "VERB"], ["come", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["comments", "NOUN"], ["subscribed", "VERB"], ["channelFollow", "VERB"], ["alliedawson", "NOUN"], ["Like", "ADP"], ["videoLeave", "NOUN"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["reach", "VERB"], ["Extra", "ADJ"], ["entry", "NOUN"], ["follow", "NOUN"], ["try", "VERB"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["start", "VERB"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["normal", "ADJ"], ["use", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["instead", "ADV"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["works", "VERB"], ["little", "ADJ"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["works", "VERB"], ["secret", "NOUN"], ["making", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["star", "VERB"], ["people", "NOUN"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["till", "SCONJ"], ["message", "VERB"], ["paying", "VERB"], ["conversation", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["referring", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["people", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["turns", "NOUN"], ["gives", "VERB"], ["start", "VERB"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["try", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["drink", "NOUN"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["turn", "NOUN"], ["spend", "VERB"], ["real", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["drinks", "NOUN"], ["order", "NOUN"], ["qualify", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["drink", "NOUN"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["joining", "VERB"], ["qualifying", "NOUN"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["promote", "VERB"], ["profile", "NOUN"], ["help", "VERB"], ["better", "ADV"], ["ranking", "NOUN"], ["help", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["personally", "ADV"], ["seeing", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["paying", "VERB"], ["promote", "VERB"], ["profile", "NOUN"], ["right", "ADV"], ["Note", "NOUN"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["receive", "VERB"], ["small", "ADJ"], ["incentive", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["subscribe", "VERB"], ["leave", "VERB"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["head", "VERB"], ["giveaway", "ADJ"], ["form", "NOUN"], ["enter", "VERB"], ["win", "VERB"], ["bars", "NOUN"], ["soap", "NOUN"], ["giveaway", "ADJ"], ["ends", "VERB"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["tend", "VERB"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["till", "SCONJ"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["recent", "ADJ"], ["payment", "NOUN"], ["proof", "NOUN"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["end", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["Cashout", "NOUN"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["signed", "VERB"], ["survey", "NOUN"], ["earning", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["right", "ADV"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["work", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["close", "ADJ"], ["quitting", "NOUN"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["open", "ADJ"], ["availability", "NOUN"], ["seriously", "ADV"], ["need", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["picking", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["total", "ADJ"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["different", "ADJ"], ["distract", "NOUN"], ["looking", "VERB"], ["seeing", "VERB"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["know", "VERB"], ["best", "ADJ"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["work", "VERB"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["split", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["Assuming", "VERB"], ["find", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["deal", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["jobs", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["income", "NOUN"], ["little", "ADJ"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["tired", "ADJ"], ["making", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["stay", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["working", "VERB"], ["stores", "NOUN"], ["need", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["pay", "VERB"], ["bills", "NOUN"], ["needs", "NOUN"], ["like", "ADP"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["moped", "VERB"], ["fixed", "VERB"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["paying", "VERB"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["owe", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["building", "VERB"], ["savings", "NOUN"], ["etc", "X"], ["giveaway", "ADJ"], ["rules", "NOUN"], ["leave", "VERB"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["pick", "VERB"], ["winner", "NOUN"], ["winner", "NOUN"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["drawing", "VERB"], ["claim", "VERB"], ["prize", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["old", "ADJ"], ["enter", "VERB"], ["giveaway", "NOUN"], ["needs", "VERB"], ["email", "VERB"], ["asap", "NOUN"], ["need", "VERB"], ["address", "NOUN"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["number", "NOUN"], ["claim", "VERB"], ["prize", "NOUN"], ["package", "NOUN"], ["mailed", "VERB"], ["email", "VERB"], ["tracking", "NOUN"], ["numberOnce", "NOUN"], ["packages", "NOUN"], ["mailed", "VERB"], ["responsible", "ADJ"], ["package", "NOUN"], ["Thank", "VERB"], ["participating", "VERB"], ["crochet", "NOUN"], ["tenstitchblanket", "NOUN"], ["started", "VERB"], ["vacation", "NOUN"], ["ball", "NOUN"], ["color", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["try", "VERB"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["decide", "VERB"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["favorite", "VERB"], ["try", "NOUN"], ["honestly", "ADV"], ["want", "VERB"], ["spot", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["tend", "VERB"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["till", "SCONJ"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["recent", "ADJ"], ["payment", "NOUN"], ["proof", "NOUN"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["end", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["Cashout", "NOUN"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["signed", "VERB"], ["survey", "NOUN"], ["earning", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["tend", "VERB"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["till", "SCONJ"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["recent", "ADJ"], ["payment", "NOUN"], ["proof", "NOUN"], ["wait", "VERB"], ["end", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["Cashout", "NOUN"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["option", "NOUN"], ["signed", "VERB"], ["survey", "NOUN"], ["earning", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["phones", "NOUN"], ["open", "ADJ"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["Starts", "VERB"], ["draw", "VERB"], ["winner", "NOUN"], ["m", "VERB"], ["solely", "ADV"], ["responsible", "ADJ"], ["giveaway", "NOUN"], ["affiliated", "VERB"], ["love", "VERB"], ["like", "VERB"], ["subscribe", "VERB"], ["check", "VERB"], ["links", "NOUN"], ["posted", "VERB"], ["great", "ADJ"], ["need", "VERB"], ["comment", "VERB"], ["ask", "VERB"], ["comment", "VERB"], ["order", "NOUN"], ["enter", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["random", "ADJ"], ["comment", "NOUN"], ["picker", "NOUN"], ["pick", "VERB"], ["winners", "NOUN"], ["review", "NOUN"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["start", "VERB"], ["saying", "VERB"], ["picture", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["got", "VERB"], ["picture", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["home", "ADV"], ["got", "VERB"], ["little", "ADJ"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["melted", "VERB"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["home", "ADV"], ["F", "NOUN"], ["jumped", "VERB"], ["box", "NOUN"], ["drive", "NOUN"], ["home", "NOUN"], ["moped", "NOUN"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["want", "VERB"], ["thank", "VERB"], ["best", "ADJ"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["sister", "NOUN"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["try", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["mystery", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["review", "NOUN"], ["rankings", "NOUN"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["cute", "ADJ"], ["sprinkles", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["Love", "VERB"], ["look", "NOUN"], ["grahams", "NOUN"], ["definitely", "ADV"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["chocolate", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["fact", "NOUN"], ["looks", "VERB"], ["like", "ADP"], ["chocolate", "NOUN"], ["cupcakes", "NOUN"], ["sold", "VERB"], ["stores", "NOUN"], ["makes", "VERB"], ["cute", "ADJ"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["peanut", "NOUN"], ["butter", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["snickers", "NOUN"], ["definitely", "ADV"], ["rankings", "NOUN"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["mystery", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["looked", "VERB"], ["like", "ADP"], ["got", "VERB"], ["home", "ADV"], ["picture", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["told", "VERB"], ["got", "VERB"], ["love", "VERB"], ["reviews", "NOUN"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["review", "NOUN"], ["able", "ADJ"], ["best", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["posting", "VERB"], ["review", "NOUN"], ["thought", "VERB"], ["pictures", "NOUN"], ["able", "ADJ"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["Hope", "VERB"], ["enjoy", "VERB"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["leave", "VERB"], ["thoughts", "NOUN"], ["comments", "NOUN"], ["tried", "VERB"], ["yummy", "ADJ"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["come", "VERB"], ["review", "NOUN"], ["names", "NOUN"], ["try", "VERB"], ["cookies", "NOUN"], ["think", "VERB"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["preferred", "VERB"], ["chocolate", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["preferred", "VERB"], ["topping", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["thumb", "NOUN"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["lucking", "VERB"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["tastes", "VERB"], ["great", "ADJ"], ["topping", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["thumbs", "NOUN"], ["favorite", "NOUN"], ["topping", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["thumbs", "NOUN"], ["looked", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["tasted", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["cookie", "NOUN"], ["thumbs", "NOUN"], ["rate", "VERB"], ["order", "NOUN"], ["liked", "VERB"], ["instead", "ADV"], ["thumbs", "NOUN"], ["following", "NOUN"], ["Honestly", "ADV"], ["tie", "NOUN"], ["place", "NOUN"], ["opinion", "NOUN"], ["place", "NOUN"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["big", "ADJ"], ["accomplishment", "NOUN"], ["drove", "VERB"], ["work", "VERB"], ["rain", "NOUN"], ["little", "ADJ"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["wind", "NOUN"], ["ish", "NOUN"], ["wind", "NOUN"], ["constant", "ADJ"], ["helped", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["wind", "NOUN"], ["speed", "NOUN"], ["constant", "ADJ"], ["try", "VERB"], ["avoid", "VERB"], ["driving", "VERB"], ["like", "ADP"], ["raining", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["avoid", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["drove", "VERB"], ["dealt", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["puddles", "NOUN"], ["sucked", "VERB"], ["wheels", "NOUN"], ["avoid", "VERB"], ["noticed", "VERB"], ["wheels", "NOUN"], ["slipped", "VERB"], ["drove", "VERB"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["slower", "ADJ"], ["attempt", "VERB"], ["wear", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["rain", "NOUN"], ["poncho", "NOUN"], ["got", "VERB"], ["work", "VERB"], ["blowing", "VERB"], ["wind", "NOUN"], ["making", "VERB"], ["blocked", "VERB"], ["views", "NOUN"], ["mirrors", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["safe", "ADJ"], ["putting", "VERB"], ["dealing", "VERB"], ["rain", "NOUN"], ["stopped", "VERB"], ["took", "VERB"], ["mention", "VERB"], ["pretty", "ADV"], ["soaked", "VERB"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["bit", "NOUN"], ["point", "NOUN"], ["think", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["encouragement", "NOUN"], ["friend", "NOUN"], ["avoid", "VERB"], ["reminded", "VERB"], ["drive", "VERB"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["like", "ADP"], ["daily", "ADV"], ["mopeds", "NOUN"], ["spent", "VERB"], ["driving", "VERB"], ["means", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["wasted", "VERB"], ["point", "NOUN"], ["trying", "VERB"], ["better", "ADV"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["confidence", "NOUN"], ["driving", "VERB"], ["rain", "NOUN"], ["like", "ADP"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["wind", "NOUN"], ["driving", "VERB"], ["general", "ADJ"], ["helps", "VERB"], ["experience", "NOUN"], ["confidence", "NOUN"], ["short", "ADJ"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["raining", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["better", "ADJ"], ["understanding", "NOUN"], ["drove", "VERB"], ["numb", "ADJ"], ["trying", "VERB"], ["process", "VERB"], ["loss", "NOUN"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["trying", "VERB"], ["deal", "VERB"], ["mom", "NOUN"], ["passing", "VERB"], ["passed", "VERB"], ["away", "ADV"], ["kinda", "ADV"], ["lost", "VERB"], ["having", "VERB"], ["trouble", "NOUN"], ["dealing", "VERB"], ["right", "ADV"], ["hitting", "VERB"], ["mom", "NOUN"], ["early", "ADV"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["loss", "NOUN"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["makes", "VERB"], ["dealing", "VERB"], ["mom", "NOUN"], ["passing", "VERB"], ["harder", "ADV"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["easy", "ADJ"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["right", "ADV"], ["got", "VERB"], ["news", "NOUN"], ["amazing", "ADJ"], ["pictures", "NOUN"], ["birthday", "NOUN"], ["memories", "NOUN"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["passed", "VERB"], ["away", "ADP"], ["evening", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["th", "X"], ["wife", "NOUN"], ["years", "NOUN"], ["good", "ADJ"], ["know", "VERB"], ["love", "VERB"], ["miss", "VERB"], ["soon", "ADV"], ["got", "VERB"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["stressed", "VERB"], ["worried", "VERB"], ["filling", "VERB"], ["paper", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["work", "VERB"], ["uber", "NOUN"], ["eats", "VERB"], ["nice", "ADJ"], ["weather", "NOUN"], ["Check", "VERB"], ["moped", "NOUN"], ["hear", "VERB"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["moped", "VERB"], ["finding", "VERB"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["place", "NOUN"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["burners", "NOUN"], ["trying", "VERB"], ["stress", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["coming", "VERB"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["giving", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["lately", "ADV"], ["consistent", "ADJ"], ["cover", "VERB"], ["bases", "NOUN"], ["find", "VERB"], ["works", "VERB"], ["better", "ADV"], ["busy", "ADJ"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["hoping", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["think", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["stocking", "NOUN"], ["yarn", "NOUN"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["like", "ADP"], ["getting", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["evening", "NOUN"], ["way", "NOUN"], ["home", "ADV"], ["working", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["having", "AUX"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["sleep", "NOUN"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["watch", "VERB"], ["stream", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["crafts", "NOUN"], ["live", "VERB"], ["wish", "VERB"], ["talk", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["advice", "NOUN"], ["situation", "NOUN"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["know", "VERB"], ["right", "ADJ"], ["thing", "NOUN"], ["ready", "ADJ"], ["scared", "ADJ"], ["losing", "VERB"], ["safety", "NOUN"], ["net", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["things", "NOUN"], ["work", "VERB"], ["postponing", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["situation", "NOUN"], ["prove", "VERB"], ["ok", "ADJ"], ["losing", "VERB"], ["safety", "NOUN"], ["net", "NOUN"], ["Played", "VERB"], ["new", "ADJ"], ["game", "NOUN"], ["honestly", "ADV"], ["love", "VERB"], ["somewhat", "ADV"], ["addicted", "ADJ"], ["livestreamed", "VERB"], ["ride", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["bad", "ADJ"], ["goal", "NOUN"], ["better", "ADV"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["earnings", "NOUN"], ["actually", "ADV"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["better", "ADV"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["happy", "ADJ"], ["hope", "VERB"], ["continue", "VERB"], ["Earnings", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["online", "ADJ"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["far", "ADV"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["send", "VERB"], ["questions", "NOUN"], ["answer", "VERB"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["paypal", "NOUN"], ["instantly", "ADV"], ["site", "NOUN"], ["play", "VERB"], ["instant", "ADJ"], ["win", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["slot", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["daily", "ADJ"], ["login", "NOUN"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["OnlyFans", "NOUN"], ["pages", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["page", "NOUN"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["page", "NOUN"], ["share", "VERB"], ["daily", "ADJ"], ["content", "NOUN"], ["spanking", "ADJ"], ["model", "NOUN"], ["work", "NOUN"], ["Current", "ADJ"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["charging", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["listening", "VERB"], ["music", "NOUN"], ["taking", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["installing", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["mainly", "ADV"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["playing", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["discover", "NOUN"], ["items", "NOUN"], ["searching", "VERB"], ["web", "NOUN"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["codes", "NOUN"], ["shopping", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["Straight", "ADJ"], ["Talk", "NOUN"], ["costumers", "NOUN"], ["thinking", "VERB"], ["Straight", "ADJ"], ["Talk", "NOUN"], ["costumers", "NOUN"], ["soon", "ADV"], ["member", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["Join", "VERB"], ["Straight", "ADJ"], ["Talk", "NOUN"], ["enroll", "VERB"], ["referral", "ADJ"], ["code", "NOUN"], ["FREE", "ADJ"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["service", "NOUN"], ["Sign", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["feel", "VERB"], ["like", "ADP"], ["people", "NOUN"], ["costumers", "NOUN"], ["forget", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["page", "NOUN"], ["win", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["add", "VERB"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["monthly", "ADJ"], ["minutes", "NOUN"], ["short", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["month", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["bill", "NOUN"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["bill", "NOUN"], ["fun", "NOUN"], ["Spin", "NOUN"], ["prizes", "NOUN"], ["avaliable", "ADJ"], ["wheel", "NOUN"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["played", "VERB"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["won", "VERB"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["played", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["perks", "NOUN"], ["local", "ADJ"], ["discounts", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["different", "ADJ"], ["ways", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["different", "ADJ"], ["ways", "NOUN"], ["redeem", "VERB"], ["points", "NOUN"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["use", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["service", "NOUN"], ["plan", "NOUN"], ["months", "NOUN"], ["short", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["helps", "VERB"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["goal", "NOUN"], ["set", "VERB"], ["progress", "NOUN"], ["far", "ADV"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["playing", "VERB"], ["game", "NOUN"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["played", "VERB"], ["laptop", "NOUN"], ["best", "ADV"], ["ranking", "NOUN"], ["far", "ADV"], ["game", "NOUN"], ["watch", "VERB"], ["stream", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["crafts", "NOUN"], ["live", "VERB"], ["delivered", "VERB"], ["deliveries", "NOUN"], ["photo", "NOUN"], ["working", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["nice", "ADJ"], ["outside", "ADV"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["send", "VERB"], ["questions", "NOUN"], ["answer", "VERB"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["paypal", "NOUN"], ["instantly", "ADV"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["blogged", "VERB"], ["free", "ADJ"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["gets", "VERB"], ["cash", "VERB"], ["gas", "NOUN"], ["Use", "VERB"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["code", "NOUN"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["gal", "ADJ"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["purchase", "NOUN"], ["reason", "NOUN"], ["save", "VERB"], ["car", "NOUN"], ["moped", "NOUN"], ["cost", "VERB"], ["alot", "NOUN"], ["fill", "VERB"], ["filling", "VERB"], ["gas", "NOUN"], ["tank", "NOUN"], ["complaining", "VERB"], ["adds", "VERB"], ["use", "VERB"], ["cashback", "NOUN"], ["add", "VERB"], ["bank", "NOUN"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["awesome", "ADJ"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["looking", "VERB"], ["wash", "NOUN"], ["looking", "VERB"], ["dish", "NOUN"], ["come", "VERB"], ["right", "ADJ"], ["place", "NOUN"], ["right", "ADV"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["send", "VERB"], ["questions", "NOUN"], ["answer", "VERB"], ["paid", "VERB"], ["paypal", "NOUN"], ["instantly", "ADV"], ["app", "NOUN"], ["blogged", "VERB"], ["looking", "VERB"], ["soap", "NOUN"], ["saver", "NOUN"], ["need", "VERB"], ["quick", "ADJ"], ["easy", "ADJ"], ["gift", "NOUN"], ["come", "VERB"], ["right", "ADJ"], ["place", "NOUN"], ["right", "ADV"], ["exciting", "ADJ"], ["day", "NOUN"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["customer", "NOUN"], ["think", "VERB"], ["gave", "VERB"], ["bill", "NOUN"], ["owed", "VERB"], ["gave", "VERB"], ["manager", "NOUN"], ["audit", "NOUN"], ["verify", "VERB"], ["correct", "ADJ"], ["lady", "NOUN"], ["going", "VERB"], ["owed", "VERB"], ["wrong", "ADJ"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["number", "NOUN"], ["regional", "ADJ"], ["manager", "NOUN"], ["complain", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["talk", "VERB"], ["kidney", "NOUN"], ["stone", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["mainly", "ADV"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["playing", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["completing", "VERB"], ["discover", "NOUN"], ["items", "NOUN"], ["searching", "VERB"], ["web", "NOUN"], ["promo", "ADJ"], ["codes", "NOUN"], ["shopping", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["lots", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["choose", "VERB"], ["search", "NOUN"], ["making", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["earning", "VERB"], ["online", "ADV"], ["time", "NOUN"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["definitely", "ADV"], ["join", "VERB"], ["heading", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["join", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["goals", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["reach", "VERB"], ["channel", "NOUN"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["Reach", "VERB"], ["followers", "NOUN"], ["captain", "NOUN"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["followers", "NOUN"], ["away", "ADV"], ["goal", "NOUN"], ["Reach", "VERB"], ["need", "VERB"], ["reach", "VERB"], ["average", "NOUN"], ["viewers", "NOUN"], ["latest", "ADJ"], ["cashout", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["charging", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["listening", "VERB"], ["music", "NOUN"], ["taking", "VERB"], ["surveys", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["installing", "VERB"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["like", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["like", "SCONJ"], ["head", "VERB"], ["link", "NOUN"], ["sign", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["reward", "NOUN"], ["options", "NOUN"], ["Counting", "VERB"], ["redemption", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["rewards", "NOUN"], ["Let", "VERB"], ["walk", "NOUN"], ["BreakMyDreamsWatch", "NOUN"], ["stream", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["crafts", "NOUN"], ["outdoor", "ADJ"], ["activities", "NOUN"], ["wanted", "VERB"], ["moment", "NOUN"], ["latest", "ADJ"], ["crocheted", "VERB"], ["project", "NOUN"], ["finished", "VERB"], ["making", "VERB"], ["yesterday", "NOUN"], ["love", "VERB"], ["tried", "VERB"], ["plan", "VERB"], ["soon", "ADV"], ["want", "VERB"], ["better", "ADJ"], ["job", "NOUN"], ["cleaning", "NOUN"], ["lasts", "VERB"], ["longer", "ADV"], ["ones", "NOUN"], ["buy", "VERB"], ["save", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["long", "ADJ"], ["run", "NOUN"], ["having", "VERB"], ["couple", "NOUN"], ["ones", "NOUN"], ["reusable", "ADJ"], ["swiffer", "NOUN"], ["mop", "NOUN"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["showing", "VERB"], ["Head", "VERB"], ["watch", "VERB"], ["video", "NOUN"], ["use", "VERB"], ["today", "NOUN"], ["daily", "ADJ"], ["login", "NOUN"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["hours", "NOUN"], ["currently", "ADV"], ["waiting", "VERB"], ["nd", "NOUN"], ["tomorrow", "NOUN"], ["morning", "NOUN"], ["like", "INTJ"], ["let", "VERB"], ["bonus", "NOUN"], ["logging", "VERB"], ["save", "NOUN"], ["start", "VERB"], ["play", "VERB"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["tend", "VERB"], ["better", "ADV"], ["instant", "ADJ"], ["win", "NOUN"], ["games", "NOUN"], ["stick", "VERB"], ["sweeps", "VERB"], ["money", "NOUN"], ["cashout", "VERB"], ["redeem", "VERB"], ["sent", "VERB"], ["bank", "NOUN"], ["account", "NOUN"], ["cashed", "VERB"], ["times", "NOUN"], ["sure", "ADJ"], ["right", "ADV"], ["hand", "NOUN"], ["guess", "VERB"], ["times", "NOUN"], ["excited", "ADJ"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["fully", "ADV"], ["tracking", "VERB"], ["online", "ADJ"], ["earnings", "NOUN"], ["head", "VERB"], ["post", "NOUN"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["bad", "ADJ"], ["start", "VERB"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["want", "VERB"], ["better", "ADV"], ["earnings", "NOUN"], ["Earnings", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["online", "ADJ"], ["sites", "NOUN"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["let", "VERB"], ["know", "VERB"], ["far", "ADV"], ["year", "NOUN"], ["favorite", "ADJ"], ["apps", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["let", "VERB"], ["run", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["week", "NOUN"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["days", "NOUN"], ["believe", "VERB"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["extra", "ADJ"], ["Mainly", "ADV"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["unlocking", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["Current", "ADJ"], ["earn", "VERB"], ["charging", "VERB"], ["phone", "NOUN"], ["watching", "VERB"], ["videos", "NOUN"], ["listening", "VERB"], ["music", "NOUN"], ["taking", "VERB"], ["surveys", "