[{"year": 2024, "entities": [["Break My Dreams Nails", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["https://www.facebook.com/groups//?mibextid=NSMWBT", "NORP"]], "lemmas": ["join", "vip", "group", "nail", "enthusiast", "want", "easy", "cheap", "way", "level", "nail", "game", "get", "access", "exclusive", "nail", "makeup", "hand", "nail", "care", "product", "plus", "expert", "tip", "trick", "help", "slay", "break", "free", "ordinary", "unleash", "creativity", "shopping", "link", "also", "want", "browse", "http", "www", "colorstreet", "com", "breakmydreamsnails", "link", "vip", "group"], "pos": [["join", "n"], ["vip", "n"], ["group", "n"], ["nail", "n"], ["enthusiasts", "n"], ["want", "v"], ["easy", "a"], ["cheap", "a"], ["way", "n"], ["level", "n"], ["nail", "n"], ["game", "n"], ["get", "n"], ["access", "n"], ["exclusive", "a"], ["nails", "n"], ["makeup", "n"], ["hand", "n"], ["nail", "n"], ["care", "n"], ["products", "n"], ["plus", null], ["expert", "a"], ["tips", "n"], ["tricks", "n"], ["help", "v"], ["slay", "v"], ["break", "n"], ["free", "a"], ["ordinary", "a"], ["unleash", "a"], ["creativity", "n"], ["shopping", "n"], ["link", "n"], ["also", "r"], ["want", "v"], ["browse", "a"], ["https", "n"], ["www", "n"], ["colorstreet", "n"], ["com", "n"], ["breakmydreamsnails", "v"], ["link", "v"], ["vip", "n"], ["group", "n"]]}, {"year": 2023, "entities": [[": Color The Cover - Composition Notebook", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Christa Sunderland", "PERSON"], ["ER", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["obese", "NORP"], ["Houseman", "PERSON"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Rosie", "PERSON"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Seated", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Ill", "GPE"], ["kinda", "GPE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["InboxDollars", "ORG"], ["PayPal", "ORG"], ["PayPal", "ORG"], ["PayPal", "ORG"], ["Tetris", "PRODUCT"], ["MyPoints", "ORG"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Dunkin' Donuts", "ORG"], ["MyPoints", "ORG"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Lindt Bear & Friends Advent Calendar", "ORG"], ["Fine Milk", "PERSON"], ["White Chocolates", "ORG"], ["Snowman Celebration Chocolate", "PERSON"], ["Cadbury Dairy", "PERSON"], ["The UK England The Very Best", "ORG"], ["British", "NORP"], ["Advent Calendar", "PERSON"], ["InchNaughty", "ORG"], ["Reese", "NORP"], ["Advent Calendar", "PERSON"], ["Candy Filled", "PERSON"], ["Spiderman", "PERSON"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Honeygain", "GPE"], ["Honeygain", "GPE"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["Honeygain", "GPE"], ["Starbucks", "ORG"], ["Wal-Mart", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Tallie", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Halloween Flameless LED Floating Candles", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Magic Wand Remote - Floating Hanging Home Decorations", "PRODUCT"], ["Skeleton Skull Lighted Holiday Displays", "PERSON"], ["Modes Waterproof Battery", "ORG"], ["Remote Timer", "ORG"], ["Banner", "ORG"], ["Hanging Swirl", "ORG"], ["Halloween Balloons", "ORG"], ["Bloody Tablecover", "ORG"], ["Handmade Pumpkin", "PERSON"], ["Cover Festive Party Supplies", "ORG"], ["Jack", "PERSON"], ["Hey Boo Autumn Table Centerpiece", "ORG"], ["Join Evidation", "PERSON"], ["Samsung Health", "ORG"], ["Twitter", "PERSON"], ["Strava", "GPE"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Hanging Witch with Bendable Arms", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Best Halloween Outdoor DecorationsJOYIN  Pack Halloween Party Decoration", "ORG"], ["Holiday Decorations", "ORG"], ["Super Stretch Cobwebs", "ORG"], ["Lantern String Lights", "PERSON"], ["Yard Sign", "PERSON"], ["Props Outdoor Decor for", "ORG"], ["Haunted House Holiday Party Supplies -  PCSJOYIN  Ft", "ORG"], ["Hairy Spider", "PERSON"], ["Large Spider", "PERSON"], ["Hairy Spider Props", "PERSON"], ["Halloween Yard Decorations Party", "ORG"], ["BlackOGWAI Halloween Projector Lights Outdoor Decorations", "ORG"], ["Hologram Decor", "PERSON"], ["Different Slides for Different Festivals - Halloween", "ORG"], ["Easter, Mother's", "ORG"], ["Giant Spiderweb, Waterproof Battery Operated", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Modes Lighted Decor", "PERSON"], ["Remote Control Halloween Decorations Indoor", "ORG"], ["Tik Tok", "PERSON"], ["Tik Tok", "PERSON"], ["Tik Tok", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Classic Snow", "PERSON"], ["Fallen Angel Costume", "PERSON"], ["Creations Adult", "PERSON"], ["Scarecrow Costume", "PERSON"], ["Join Robinhood", "PERSON"], ["Robinhood", "PRODUCT"], ["at least $", "MONEY"], ["Robinhood", "FAC"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Jumpsuit Costume", "PERSON"], ["Adult", "PERSON"], ["Air Costume for", "ORG"], ["Mandalorian", "NORP"], ["Armor Adult CostumeSATINIOR", "ORG"], ["Mens Costume", "PERSON"], ["Slip", "PERSON"], ["Costume Party", "ORG"], ["Trick or Treating, Cosplay PartyDouble Couple Halloween Costumes for Men Women with Scary Light up", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Costumes Cloak", "PERSON"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Shopkick", "PERSON"], ["Shopkick", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Cowboy Costume", "PERSON"], ["Scarf", "ORG"], ["EarringsLuucio Girls Police Officer Costume for Kids", "ORG"], ["Role Play Kit", "PERSON"], ["GirlsChild Royal Vampire", "ORG"], ["Cheerleader Costume", "PERSON"], ["Headband WingPeach Costume", "FAC"], ["Inflatable Costumes for Kids", "ORG"], ["Inflatable Costume", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Mask Skeleton Gloves Set", "PERSON"], ["Glow Gloves", "PERSON"], ["Headwear Cartoon Game Outfit for - Years", "EVENT"], ["Cop Costume Role Play Kit", "PERSON"], ["Sided Superhero Capes & Costumes Set for Kids - Ideal", "ORG"], ["Cosplay - Unique Designs for Boys & Girls", "PERSON"], ["Role Play - Perfect Dress-", "PERSON"], ["Gift Idea", "PERSON"], ["Jumpsuit forDolxico", "PERSON"], ["Morphsuits Zalgo Costume Kids, The Rake Costume Kids, Monster Costume Kids, Scary Halloween Costumes for BoysDisguise Toddler Blippi CostumeSicypoty Kids Skeleton Costume Glow in the Dark Halloween Costume for Boys BlackMorph Dragon Costume Kids", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["SKITTLES Original", "PERSON"], ["SKITTLES Wild Berry", "PERSON"], ["Original & LIFE SAVERS Gummies", "ORG"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Skittles", "PERSON"], ["Swedish", "NORP"], ["Air Heads", "ORG"], ["Jolly Rancher", "PERSON"], ["Sour Punch", "PERSON"], ["Haribo Gold-Bears Gummi", "PERSON"], ["Candy - Candy Bulk", "PERSON"], ["Sour Patch", "PERSON"], ["Lollipops, Lifesavers", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Sour Candy", "PERSON"], ["Tootsie Rolls", "PERSON"], ["Party Mix -  Pounds", "PERSON"], ["Candy Bulk - Variety Parade Candies - Pinata Candies - Individually Wrapped", "PERSON"], ["Pounds - Assorted", "PERSON"], ["Candy Bulk", "PERSON"], ["Candy - Bulk", "PERSON"], ["Mixed Bag", "PERSON"], ["Individually Wrapped Trick", "PERSON"], ["Treat Candy", "PERSON"], ["Nerds", "GPE"], ["Gummy Candy Body Parts", "PERSON"], ["Jack", "PERSON"], ["Lantern, Ghost & Witch", "ORG"], ["Giant Mix - Pinata", "PERSON"], ["Carawlers", "PERSON"], ["Jaw Busters", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Hershey Assorted Flavored Miniatures", "ORG"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Piece )", "ORG"], ["Candy Bulk", "PERSON"], ["KIT KAT", "ORG"], ["REESE'S Assorted Milk Chocolate Candy Variety Box", "ORG"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Assorted Milk Chocolate", "ORG"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Candy Bulk Bag", "PERSON"], ["Assorted Milk Chocolate", "ORG"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Caramel Flavors Miniatures", "ORG"], ["Candy Variety Bag", "PERSON"], ["Giveaway Details", "PERSON"], ["IG", "ORG"], ["Rebel Rouge Labs", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Eastern Standard Time", "LOC"], ["Winner", "PERSON"], ["ShezGotYarn", "ORG"], ["#", "CARDINAL"], ["#", "CARDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["the Red Heart  ", "ORG"], ["Jumbo Yarn", "PERSON"], ["Newspaper  Stripe", "PERSON"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["the Crumble Cookies", "ORG"], ["all three", "CARDINAL"], ["Brownie Batter", "PRODUCT"], ["Peanut Butter  Cup", "PERSON"], ["Double Chocolate  Chip", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["The Giveaway", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["USA", "GPE"], ["YouTube", "ORG"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["Crumble Cookies", "ORG"], ["Otter", "PERSON"], ["four", "CARDINAL"], ["Tasty", "PERSON"], ["Honey Cake Cookie: Tasty", "PERSON"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Peanut Butter Cookie:", "PERSON"], ["Honey Cake Cookie", "PERSON"], ["Peanut Butter Cookie", "PERSON"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["Otter", "PERSON"], ["them?Cotton Candy - Pretty", "FAC"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"], ["Birthday Cake - This", "PERSON"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"], ["Caramel Shortbread - This cookie", "PERSON"], ["Two", "CARDINAL"], ["Birthday Cake", "PERSON"], ["Caramel Shortbread", "PERSON"], ["Peanut Butter", "PERSON"], ["Cotton Candy", "PERSON"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["fourth", "ORDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Walmart", "ORG"], ["Brian Croxford", "PERSON"], ["TON", "ORG"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Papa", "ORG"], ["Papa", "ORG"], ["Papa", "PERSON"], ["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Papa", "PERSON"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Sally", "PERSON"], ["Q  - $", "PERSON"], ["Luckyland Slots - $", "PERSON"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Swagbucks - $", "LAW"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["Straight Talk", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Rewards", "NORP"], ["Straight Talk", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Straight Talk", "PERSON"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Wormate.io", "ORG"], ["https://www.twitch.tv/breakmydreams Yayness", "PERSON"], ["https://www.uber.com/us/en/s/c/deliver/?invite_code=ztsjjwsrz", "PERSON"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["CHRISTA", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["https://ko-fi.com/s/f Q  -", "PERSON"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Twitch", "PERSON"], ["Stream Raiders", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Swiffer", "NORP"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Telephia - $", "ORG"], ["Uber Eats - $", "PERSON"], ["KissMyCash", "GPE"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Telephia", "ORG"], ["Android", "ORG"], ["Apple", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["Love Hersheys Doughnuts", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Canadian", "NORP"], ["Krispy Kreme", "PERSON"], ["Puerto Rico", "GPE"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["Krispy Kreme Doughnut Corp.", "PERSON"], ["KREMETM Doughnut", "PERSON"], ["KREMETM", "ORG"], ["KREMETM", "ORG"], ["Strawberry Dream Doughnut", "PERSON"], ["KREMETM", "ORG"], ["Kreme", "PERSON"], ["KREMETM", "ORG"], ["Valentine", "PERSON"], ["Day Assortment", "ORG"], ["strawberry", "PERSON"], ["Valentines Day", "LOC"], ["Main Prize Category -First Place:  Oval Chevron Embossed Metal Sign", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Second", "MONEY"], ["Tombstone Hot & Cold", "ORG"], ["eGift CardsNo", "PERSON"], ["U.S.", "GPE"], ["SocialToaster Advocate", "ORG"], ["SocialToaster", "ORG"], ["DSRL", "ORG"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["DSLR", "ORG"], ["EOS", "ORG"], ["megapixel stills", "ORG"], ["three", "CARDINAL"], ["EF", "ORG"], ["EOS", "ORG"], ["Rs", "PRODUCT"], ["RF mount", "PRODUCT"], ["We're", "PERSON"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Don't", "CARDINAL"], ["ten", "CARDINAL"], ["videomaker.com", "ORG"], ["USA", "GPE"], ["This Nintendo Switch", "PERSON"], ["Nintendo Switch", "PERSON"], ["CDnd", "NORP"], ["the Cozy Mystery Tribe", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["five", "CARDINAL"], ["Gift BasketPrize", "PERSON"], ["Gift BasketBy", "PERSON"], ["the The Cozy Mystery Tribe", "ORG"], ["US", "GPE"], ["Giveaways", "PERSON"], ["Sweepstakes", "PERSON"], ["Dollar Tree", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["OnlyFans - $", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["KissMyCash", "GPE"], ["KissMyCash", "GPE"], ["GPT", "ORG"], ["KissMyCash", "GPE"], ["subspace?\"Broadly", "ORDINAL"], ["subspace", "ORG"], ["Dominant", "ORG"], ["Topspace", "PERSON"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["One", "CARDINAL"], ["Fantasy Books Bundle", "PERSON"], ["Gift Card - Giveaway -  ", "PERSON"], ["Epic Book Series", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Barnes", "PERSON"], ["J.R.R. Tolkien", "PERSON"], ["The Hobbit & The Lord of the Rings", "ORG"], ["Mistborn TrilogyB. Sanderson", "PERSON"], ["E. Feist", "PERSON"], ["J. Wurts & Feist: Empire", "ORG"], ["TrilogyAll", "ORG"], ["Change of Fortune: A Fateful Force Origins Story", "ORG"], ["The Tome of SyyxMake", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["St. Patrick's", "GPE"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Easter", "PERSON"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Enter For Free", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Thanksgiving Day", "EVENT"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Black Friday", "EVENT"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["New Year Day", "EVENT"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Gibson Custom Les", "PERSON"], ["Trade Guitars", "ORG"], ["one", "CARDINAL"], ["Gibson Custom Les Paul  Reissue VOS", "PERSON"], ["Candy Apple Green", "ORG"], ["the Les Paul", "ORG"], ["Trade Guitars", "ORG"], ["YouTube", "ORG"], ["NSFW", "ORG"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Paypal", "PERSON"], ["Amazon", "ORG"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["Tallie", "PERSON"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["Brian Croxford", "PERSON"], ["Nicole Rhodes", "PERSON"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["NC", "GPE"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["OnlyFans", "NORP"], ["Fansly", "ORG"], ["OnlyFans", "NORP"], ["Fansly", "ORG"], ["Fansly", "ORG"], ["OnlyFans", "NORP"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["https://www.twitch.tv/breakmydreams", "PERSON"], ["BingoPort", "ORG"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["BingoPort", "ORG"], ["Port Points", "ORG"], ["Port Points", "ORG"], ["Port Points", "FAC"], ["BingoPort Bulletin", "FAC"], ["Port Points", "FAC"], ["Port Points", "ORG"], ["Swagbucks", "PERSON"], ["Port Points", "FAC"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Starbucks", "ORG"], ["Wal-Mart", "ORG"], ["Dollar Tree", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["Telephia - $", "ORG"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["Amazon - $", "ORG"], ["Cashback", "PERSON"], ["Bank Of America - $", "ORG"], ["Bank Of America", "ORG"], ["Uber Eats - $", "PERSON"], ["Uber Eats", "PERSON"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["Shopkick", "PERSON"], ["Shopkick", "PERSON"], ["Uber Eats", "PERSON"], ["third", "ORDINAL"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Aloe Vera", "ORG"], ["Golden Hearts Games - $", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["UserTesting - $", "ORG"], ["Amazon Mechanical Turk - $", "ORG"], ["two", "CARDINAL"], ["Amazon - $", "ORG"], ["$.Gift Cards", "MONEY"], ["$.Total", "MONEY"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["first", "ORDINAL"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Dollar Tree", "WORK_OF_ART"], ["second", "ORDINAL"], ["Richmond", "GPE"], ["VA", "GPE"], ["DMV", "ORG"]], "lemmas": ["check", "new", "book", "christmas", "cover", "paperback", "december", "author", "find", "https", "amzn", "rfacq", "enjoyable", "podcast", "think", "actually", "follow", "disciplined", "dream", "job", "instead", "always", "slack", "get", "go", "well", "awhile", "could", "actually", "make", "worth", "live", "longterm", "stop", "slacking", "go", "well", "stay", "discipline", "another", "kidney", "stone", "find", "yesterday", "quite", "bit", "pain", "nauseate", "honestly", "get", "deal", "kidney", "stone", "surprise", "anymore", "live", "tell", "doctor", "immediately", "see", "dehydrate", "honestly", "stay", "hydrate", "well", "surprising", "dehydrate", "well", "however", "news", "get", "huge", "wake", "call", "go", "work", "change", "thing", "avoid", "get", "worse", "honestly", "want", "anything", "health", "scare", "go", "easy", "change", "need", "necessary", "also", "call", "overweight", "something", "use", "fan", "hear", "brings", "back", "memories", "bully", "elementary", "school", "young", "hurt", "morning", "deal", "earache", "hoping", "go", "away", "soon", "get", "bad", "job", "look", "require", "experience", "pay", "well", "get", "wrong", "love", "housekeep", "favorite", "cashier", "stock", "favorite", "far", "housekeep", "pay", "hourly", "housekeeper", "look", "new", "job", "experience", "pay", "since", "experience", "also", "need", "job", "full", "time", "part", "time", "ca", "make", "end", "meet", "part", "time", "would", "part", "time", "job", "would", "actually", "give", "hour", "time", "make", "work", "well", "pay", "also", "would", "love", "another", "job", "get", "overtime", "would", "get", "trouble", "job", "hunt", "work", "content", "creator", "online", "work", "craft", "mystery", "shopping", "livestreaming", "job", "full", "time", "well", "actually", "pay", "well", "make", "live", "hey", "check", "app", "earn", "money", "back", "every", "meal", "use", "link", "sign", "get", "bonus", "meal", "get", "https", "seat", "app", "link", "eqeqywzdb", "kinda", "pickle", "work", "feel", "like", "go", "lose", "job", "base", "stocking", "manager", "tell", "go", "start", "stocker", "go", "start", "write", "stock", "box", "hour", "normal", "stocking", "day", "well", "write", "ups", "thing", "put", "correct", "uboats", "pallet", "truck", "day", "base", "say", "yesterday", "likely", "write", "uboat", "box", "mean", "take", "half", "hour", "complete", "take", "entire", "shift", "meaning", "super", "thin", "ice", "work", "previous", "write", "ups", "go", "lose", "job", "write", "stock", "box", "fast", "enough", "let", "get", "overthinking", "put", "position", "post", "make", "dollar", "tree", "reddit", "page", "ask", "number", "report", "violation", "annousmously", "store", "manager", "saw", "ask", "end", "tell", "felt", "like", "violation", "text", "tell", "get", "number", "case", "confident", "enough", "go", "yet", "call", "anything", "say", "could", "want", "though", "mention", "want", "come", "wait", "call", "mention", "stocking", "manager", "say", "feel", "like", "go", "lose", "job", "write", "really", "want", "happen", "reply", "yet", "fair", "yesterday", "thanksgiving", "mention", "want", "put", "truck", "day", "instead", "mean", "less", "chance", "lose", "job", "write", "stock", "enough", "box", "hour", "hate", "though", "really", "need", "hour", "week", "work", "hour", "work", "actually", "bring", "enough", "money", "pay", "bill", "save", "money", "well", "go", "lose", "lose", "job", "another", "write", "go", "back", "hour", "week", "mention", "would", "like", "good", "training", "know", "many", "box", "hour", "stock", "hour", "would", "feel", "comfortable", "stock", "worrying", "write", "lose", "job", "love", "stock", "job", "want", "continue", "work", "stock", "actually", "like", "work", "dollar", "tree", "particuallary", "store", "work", "employee", "costumer", "know", "come", "time", "sigh", "stress", "feeling", "like", "go", "fired", "vacation", "day", "somehow", "get", "lucky", "lose", "job", "lose", "hour", "even", "though", "hour", "holiday", "go", "upset", "need", "hour", "week", "hour", "week", "amazing", "past", "month", "anyways", "need", "finish", "get", "ready", "work", "morning", "need", "get", "stress", "cry", "super", "crappy", "week", "general", "kinda", "quiet", "hide", "avoid", "people", "afraid", "take", "step", "find", "good", "job", "afraid", "lose", "currently", "afraid", "find", "new", "job", "like", "lose", "jobless", "afraid", "position", "kinda", "comfortable", "current", "job", "without", "hour", "part", "time", "work", "realize", "much", "lose", "lose", "current", "job", "new", "job", "work", "lose", "everything", "work", "convince", "take", "next", "step", "find", "job", "pays", "time", "experience", "worth", "sigh", "recent", "cashout", "cash", "reward", "alot", "gift", "card", "choice", "fan", "need", "current", "time", "earn", "survey", "videos", "promo", "code", "game", "offer", "member", "yet", "would", "like", "join", "head", "link", "today", "join", "need", "help", "join", "let", "know", "share", "earn", "recently", "see", "lifetime", "earnings", "remind", "play", "fruit", "play", "head", "http", "suikagame", "io", "think", "play", "game", "yet", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "http", "www", "twitch", "tv", "breakmydreams", "see", "make", "another", "cashout", "another", "gift", "card", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "promo", "code", "search", "web", "complete", "offer", "lots", "reward", "besides", "gift", "card", "choose", "well", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "make", "earning", "online", "full", "time", "job", "site", "defiantly", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "see", "make", "another", "cashout", "reward", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "lot", "reward", "choose", "besides", "well", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "make", "earning", "online", "full", "time", "job", "site", "definitely", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "know", "alone", "count", "christmas", "get", "close", "know", "always", "love", "still", "love", "advent", "calendar", "countdown", "christmas", "want", "share", "one", "find", "hope", "enjoy", "let", "know", "get", "well", "gmadelaine", "chocolate", "advent", "calendar", "premium", "milk", "chocolates", "oz", "gram", "advent", "calendar", "countdown", "christmas", "ozoriginal", "milk", "advent", "calendar", "imported", "dairy", "milk", "chocolatehershey", "miniatures", "candy", "filled", "christmas", "nice", "chocolate", "advent", "calendar", "countdown", "christmas", "pieces", "peanut", "butter", "cup", "chocolate", "countdown", "christmas", "days", "pack", "hershey", "milk", "chocolate", "kisses", "christmas", "advent", "calendargalerie", "marvel", "advent", "calendar", "days", "countdown", "christmas", "milk", "chocolate", "pieces", "ounces", "blueelf", "shelf", "milk", "chocolate", "christmas", "advent", "countdown", "calendar", "oz", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "use", "app", "almost", "year", "believe", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "cashout", "might", "less", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "see", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "paypal", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earn", "site", "use", "make", "money", "make", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "payment", "method", "choose", "image", "mind", "since", "love", "use", "alot", "use", "awhile", "cashout", "wait", "awhile", "cash", "see", "app", "let", "run", "background", "device", "check", "app", "free", "point", "daily", "show", "honey", "jar", "cashout", "wo", "last", "either", "love", "apps", "let", "run", "make", "money", "show", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "love", "app", "use", "years", "earn", "reward", "mainly", "cashout", "gift", "card", "gift", "card", "one", "tempt", "get", "day", "cash", "another", "reward", "today", "october", "use", "app", "unlock", "phone", "also", "occasionally", "watch", "video", "earn", "point", "well", "also", "download", "apps", "play", "game", "earn", "extra", "point", "well", "would", "like", "earn", "reward", "unlock", "phone", "well", "like", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "start", "earn", "reward", "sighs", "comment", "earlier", "make", "think", "ex", "boyfriend", "even", "really", "sure", "make", "want", "cry", "part", "still", "feel", "ex", "boyfriend", "wish", "able", "friend", "cut", "life", "way", "leave", "comment", "make", "think", "sigh", "leave", "wrong", "way", "wish", "could", "go", "back", "leave", "correct", "way", "hurt", "badly", "ca", "learn", "ever", "get", "another", "relationship", "thing", "guy", "fair", "though", "see", "happen", "sigh", "ex", "boyfriend", "good", "guy", "perfect", "neither", "still", "grow", "alot", "since", "leave", "grow", "well", "grow", "leave", "time", "life", "need", "learn", "adult", "independent", "thank", "also", "worst", "part", "life", "pass", "away", "yeah", "keep", "alive", "along", "cat", "wish", "still", "leave", "live", "stable", "fair", "sigh", "yeah", "go", "kinda", "leave", "need", "get", "sigh", "hop", "mood", "headspace", "get", "memory", "ex", "boyfriend", "mess", "honestly", "stress", "enough", "feel", "like", "fail", "live", "go", "lose", "worked", "thing", "change", "job", "wise", "well", "continue", "make", "independent", "responsible", "adult", "choice", "feel", "like", "struggle", "still", "hate", "wo", "help", "take", "step", "new", "job", "sigh", "memory", "suck", "relationship", "suck", "adult", "suck", "emotion", "suck", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "decoration", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "outdoor", "decoration", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "pc", "spooky", "atmosphere", "perfect", "festive", "home", "displaygivalue", "halloween", "lantern", "string", "lights", "led", "decorative", "lanterns", "pumpkin", "ghost", "bat", "lights", "string", "plug", "ft", "indoor", "outdoor", "halloween", "decorations", "white", "ghost", "halloween", "leds", "operated", "lighted", "holiday", "displays", "remote", "spooky", "decorations", "indoor", "outdoor", "warm", "yellow", "pack", "genswin", "halloween", "flameless", "votive", "candles", "color", "changing", "battery", "operated", "led", "tealight", "candles", "halloween", "home", "decoration", "gifts", "pack", "battery", "included", "pack", "halloween", "party", "decorations", "set", "halloween", "window", "clings", "bat", "wall", "decal", "perfect", "outdoor", "indoor", "halloween", "decorationsfunpeny", "halloween", "decorations", "indoor", "inch", "wooden", "nutcrackers", "figures", "decor", "table", "fireplace", "desk", "man", "jack", "lantern", "pumpkin", "candy", "bucketaerwo", "halloween", "decoration", "black", "lace", "spiderweb", "fireplace", "mantle", "scarf", "cm", "inchvanthylit", "black", "spooky", "tree", "glittered", "led", "purple", "lights", "bat", "decorations", "battery", "powered", "halloween", "tree", "decoration", "tabletop", "home", "indoor", "decor", "ft", "timer", "meonum", "pack", "halloween", "decorations", "indoor", "halloween", "candles", "battery", "operated", "halloween", "flameless", "candles", "led", "skeleton", "hands", "hold", "candle", "halloween", "centerpiece", "tables", "fireplace", "party", "decorhalloween", "ghost", "candle", "scene", "bowl", "candle", "glow", "dark", "lantern", "fall", "scented", "holiday", "decoration", "gift", "set", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "get", "pay", "healthy", "connect", "apps", "start", "earn", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "give", "example", "apps", "connect", "evidation", "earn", "point", "connect", "mine", "apps", "connect", "use", "see", "earn", "total", "app", "since", "late", "cashout", "current", "october", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "would", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "current", "today", "reward", "option", "well", "counting", "redemption", "make", "reward", "reward", "since", "october", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "decoration", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "outdoor", "decoration", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "joyin", "pack", "halloween", "indoor", "outdoor", "decorationsjoyin", "pack", "hanging", "halloween", "skeleton", "ghosts", "decorations", "grim", "reapers", "hanging", "ghosts", "cute", "flying", "ghost", "front", "yard", "patio", "lawn", "garden", "party", "decor", "sqft", "spider", "webs", "halloween", "decorations", "bonus", "fake", "spiders", "halloween", "indoor", "outdoor", "party", "suppliesgivalue", "halloween", "led", "decorative", "lanterns", "pumpkin", "ghost", "bat", "lights", "string", "plug", "ft", "connectable", "indoor", "outdoor", "halloween", "decorations", "orange", "pumpkin", "halloween", "decorations", "outdoor", "scary", "zombie", "vampire", "graves", "lawn", "decorations", "beware", "warning", "stakes", "halloween", "outdoor", "decorations", "scary", "giant", "spider", "fake", "decor", "halloween", "window", "projector", "christmas", "birthday", "dayspider", "web", "halloween", "decoration", "outdoor", "lights", "purple", "led", "light", "ft", "halloween", "decor", "outdoor", "yard", "outsidepcs", "halloween", "decorations", "outdoor", "halloween", "lights", "witch", "hats", "ft", "lighting", "modes", "string", "lights", "tree", "patio", "yard", "party", "decor", "halloween", "decor", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "follow", "subscribe", "subscribe", "get", "sub", "live", "stream", "like", "song", "request", "direct", "message", "comment", "response", "shoutout", "behind", "scene", "video", "cost", "month", "subscribe", "hope", "see", "soon", "subscribe", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "women", "hippie", "costume", "set", "halloween", "hippie", "dress", "bell", "bottom", "boho", "flared", "pant", "dress", "partyspooktacular", "creations", "halloween", "ninja", "warrior", "costume", "women", "ninja", "maskleg", "avenue", "womens", "white", "set", "family", "friend", "full", "length", "princess", "dressabaowedding", "womens", "medieval", "renaissance", "costume", "cosplay", "dressrubies", "women", "dc", "comics", "wonder", "woman", "shirt", "cape", "headbandspooktacular", "creations", "adult", "women", "police", "costumesexy", "kranchungel", "renaissance", "dresses", "women", "costume", "fairy", "renaissance", "dress", "ball", "gown", "medieval", "irish", "peasant", "dress", "pcs", "outfits", "women", "hippie", "costume", "set", "peace", "sign", "earring", "headband", "fringe", "vest", "tassel", "cardiganspooktacular", "women", "scary", "halloween", "dress", "party", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "link", "pick", "free", "stock", "sign", "herein", "order", "get", "free", "stock", "set", "account", "link", "bank", "account", "see", "get", "least", "stock", "range", "lead", "company", "stock", "join", "may", "invest", "alot", "stock", "choose", "perform", "well", "also", "let", "know", "know", "much", "stock", "market", "work", "learn", "picked", "stock", "see", "family", "member", "stock", "wise", "performing", "time", "work", "favor", "far", "stock", "different", "one", "back", "wednesday", "february", "cash", "work", "building", "stock", "helpful", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "spooktacular", "creations", "taco", "costume", "adult", "deluxe", "set", "halloween", "dress", "partyspooktacular", "creations", "pickle", "halloween", "dress", "trick", "treatingspooktacular", "creations", "appealing", "banana", "costume", "adult", "deluxe", "set", "halloween", "dress", "party", "roleplay", "cosplaydoscos", "adult", "inflatable", "dinosaur", "costume", "funny", "halloween", "costumes", "men", "women", "riding", "rex", "blow", "party", "rubies", "star", "wars", "beskar", "halloween", "cosplay", "accessories", "outfit", "gangster", "vest", "fedora", "hat", "pocket", "watch", "suspendersbeverage", "costume", "halloween", "costume", "women", "men", "size", "fits", "allspooktacular", "creations", "adult", "men", "pirate", "costume", "halloween", "mask", "vampire", "witch", "cape", "cosplay", "hoodadult", "onesie", "halloween", "costume", "animal", "sea", "creature", "plush", "piece", "cosplay", "suit", "adults", "women", "men", "funziez", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "hi", "think", "love", "free", "app", "reward", "shop", "brand", "love", "even", "visit", "store", "sign", "code", "get", "bonus", "kick", "use", "code", "easy", "cash", "reward", "time", "since", "start", "use", "app", "back", "july", "reward", "shop", "store", "online", "already", "make", "use", "earn", "reward", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "zfqi", "girls", "movie", "pink", "cowgirl", "uniform", "set", "police", "costume", "kids", "halloween", "costume", "girls", "costumetchh", "kids", "halloween", "skeleton", "costume", "boy", "girl", "print", "jumpsuits", "size", "yearsamobon", "halloween", "maleficent", "costume", "kids", "evil", "queen", "witch", "dress", "wings", "horns", "cape", "girls", "cosplay", "carnival", "partygirls", "halloween", "party", "uniform", "dress", "kidssoyoekbt", "girls", "unicorn", "costume", "led", "light", "unicorn", "princess", "tutu", "dress", "birthday", "party", "halloween", "girls", "led", "light", "princess", "peach", "dress", "accessories", "halloween", "cosplay", "dress", "uprquxmt", "blow", "party", "costume", "dog", "halloween", "costumes", "boys", "girlsspooktacular", "creations", "fairytale", "witch", "cute", "witch", "costume", "deluxe", "set", "broom", "girls", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "need", "costume", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "costume", "get", "hand", "time", "halloween", "sago", "brothers", "halloween", "light", "scary", "led", "mask", "halloween", "costumes", "boys", "girlsprinlky", "skibidi", "toilet", "boys", "costume", "halloween", "cosplay", "party", "bodysuits", "kidsjoycover", "police", "officer", "costume", "kids", "police", "uniform", "kids", "kids", "halloween", "costumes", "boys", "girls", "toddler", "dress", "halloween", "career", "daypremium", "double", "halloween", "christmas", "games", "kowshdcs", "kids", "halloween", "costume", "boys", "superhero", "cosplay", "bodysuit", "spandex", "inflatable", "dinosaur", "costume", "kids", "halloween", "ride", "rex", "dino", "blow", "dinosaur", "costume", "kids", "size", "funny", "inflatable", "halloween", "costumes", "kids", "boys", "girls", "colors", "dragon", "costumes", "boys", "halloween", "costumes", "boys", "kids", "dragon", "costume", "boys", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "candy", "trick", "treater", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "candy", "get", "hands", "time", "halloween", "give", "trick", "treater", "starburst", "bulk", "halloween", "pieces", "halloween", "bulk", "assorted", "fruit", "candy", "starburst", "fish", "sour", "patch", "kids", "bears", "twizzlers", "oz", "variety", "pack", "bulk", "candy", "variety", "pack", "lb", "halloween", "individually", "wrapped", "candy", "kid", "pez", "smarties", "pinata", "candy", "stuffersbulk", "halloween", "trick", "treating", "assorted", "candyhalloween", "bulk", "pinata", "candy", "halloween", "bulk", "candies", "party", "goodie", "bag", "stuffers", "kids", "birthday", "trick", "treat", "candies", "halloween", "parade", "individually", "wrapped", "candiesghost", "goodies", "assorted", "halloween", "candy", "ct", "sweetarts", "trolli", "laffy", "taffyfrankford", "halloween", "count", "fusion", "select", "halloween", "candy", "lollipops", "halloween", "suckers", "trick", "treat", "candies", "kids", "frankenstein", "monster", "hat", "halloween", "sweets", "individually", "wrapped", "treats", "per", "boxhalloween", "candy", "variety", "pack", "count", "stuffers", "parade", "mixes", "pound", "bulk", "candy", "assorted", "individually", "wrapped", "candy", "party", "mix", "candy", "assortment", "includes", "trolli", "smarties", "later", "super", "bubble", "gum", "lemonheadsour", "patch", "kids", "big", "individually", "wrapped", "soft", "chewy", "candy", "halloween", "candy", "count", "box", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "halloween", "come", "big", "night", "candy", "trick", "treater", "think", "would", "good", "thing", "share", "find", "candy", "get", "hands", "time", "halloween", "give", "trick", "treater", "halloween", "oz", "hershey", "assorted", "milk", "chocolate", "creme", "flavors", "snack", "size", "halloween", "variety", "bag", "oz", "pieces", "hershey", "oz", "count", "hershey", "assorted", "milk", "chocolate", "pumpkin", "flavors", "snack", "size", "halloween", "bulk", "oz", "count", "hershey", "assorted", "milk", "chocolate", "coconut", "flavors", "snack", "size", "halloween", "bulk", "oz", "count", "hershey", "miniatures", "assorted", "chocolate", "candy", "party", "pack", "ozhershey", "fruit", "flavors", "snack", "size", "halloween", "bulk", "oz", "count", "reese", "miniatures", "milk", "chocolate", "peanut", "butter", "cups", "halloween", "ozhershey", "coconut", "flavors", "snack", "size", "halloween", "bulk", "oz", "count", "hershey", "assorted", "milk", "chocolate", "halloween", "bulk", "oz", "count", "note", "link", "post", "may", "contain", "affiliate", "link", "use", "cost", "anything", "extra", "qualify", "purchase", "may", "receive", "small", "commension", "make", "sure", "go", "actual", "video", "comment", "get", "enter", "win", "giveaway", "good", "luck", "win", "come", "back", "let", "u", "know", "comment", "subscribe", "channelfollow", "alliedawson", "like", "videoleave", "comment", "reach", "extra", "entry", "follow", "ighttps", "rebelrougelabs", "bigcartel", "com", "get", "try", "site", "today", "would", "rather", "start", "site", "normal", "use", "link", "instead", "site", "work", "little", "bit", "site", "work", "see", "secret", "make", "money", "site", "star", "many", "people", "wait", "till", "message", "pay", "conversation", "also", "earn", "site", "refer", "new", "people", "sign", "link", "turn", "give", "start", "site", "try", "get", "free", "drink", "friend", "must", "turn", "spend", "real", "money", "free", "drink", "order", "qualify", "do", "earn", "free", "drink", "friend", "join", "qualify", "see", "also", "pay", "promote", "profile", "help", "give", "good", "rank", "help", "earn", "money", "site", "personally", "do", "yet", "see", "earn", "without", "pay", "promote", "profile", "right", "note", "may", "referral", "link", "post", "receive", "small", "incentive", "use", "go", "subscribe", "leave", "comment", "video", "head", "giveaway", "form", "google", "enter", "win", "bar", "soap", "giveaway", "end", "tuesday", "september", "use", "app", "almost", "year", "believe", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "cashout", "might", "less", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "see", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "paypal", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earn", "site", "use", "make", "money", "make", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "right", "currently", "work", "part", "time", "job", "really", "close", "quit", "post", "currently", "open", "availability", "seriously", "need", "part", "time", "job", "pick", "free", "hour", "another", "dollar", "tree", "ca", "go", "total", "hour", "week", "even", "different", "distract", "look", "see", "get", "part", "time", "job", "know", "best", "way", "make", "day", "work", "job", "split", "day", "job", "find", "part", "time", "job", "assuming", "ca", "find", "another", "full", "time", "job", "deal", "part", "time", "job", "make", "full", "time", "job", "income", "little", "work", "tire", "make", "enough", "money", "stay", "hour", "week", "work", "store", "need", "money", "come", "pay", "bill", "need", "like", "get", "mop", "fix", "get", "new", "phone", "pay", "back", "friend", "owe", "money", "building", "saving", "etc", "giveaway", "rule", "please", "leave", "comment", "pick", "winner", "july", "pm", "winner", "day", "day", "draw", "claim", "prize", "must", "year", "old", "enter", "giveaway", "need", "email", "asap", "shezgotyarn", "dormeyers", "comi", "need", "address", "phone", "number", "claim", "prize", "package", "mail", "email", "track", "numberonce", "package", "mail", "responsible", "package", "thank", "participate", "front", "back", "crochet", "tenstitchblanket", "start", "vacation", "ball", "super", "saver", "color", "frontback", "get", "try", "week", "really", "love", "cooky", "ca", "decide", "favorite", "least", "favorite", "give", "try", "honestly", "want", "put", "top", "spot", "week", "use", "app", "almost", "year", "believe", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "cashout", "might", "less", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "see", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "paypal", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earn", "site", "use", "make", "money", "make", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "use", "app", "almost", "year", "believe", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "cashout", "might", "less", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "see", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "paypal", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earn", "site", "use", "make", "money", "make", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "open", "canada", "must", "year", "old", "starts", "june", "ends", "june", "draw", "winner", "sometime", "june", "solely", "responsible", "giveaway", "affiliated", "giveaway", "would", "love", "would", "like", "subscribe", "could", "check", "link", "post", "would", "great", "need", "comment", "ask", "comment", "order", "enter", "use", "random", "comment", "picker", "pick", "winner", "review", "cooky", "week", "want", "start", "say", "get", "picture", "get", "got", "picture", "get", "home", "get", "little", "bit", "melted", "way", "home", "jump", "around", "box", "drive", "home", "mop", "still", "good", "also", "want", "say", "thank", "best", "friend", "sister", "get", "try", "know", "name", "mystery", "cookie", "review", "ranking", "cooky", "mystery", "cookie", "cookie", "cute", "sprinkle", "top", "would", "get", "cookie", "love", "look", "teddy", "graham", "top", "would", "definitely", "get", "chocolate", "mallow", "cupcake", "cookie", "ca", "go", "wrong", "chocolate", "cookie", "fact", "look", "like", "chocolate", "cupcake", "sell", "store", "make", "cute", "would", "get", "ca", "go", "wrong", "peanut", "butter", "cookie", "snicker", "top", "would", "definitely", "get", "ranking", "cooky", "chocolate", "mallow", "cupcake", "cookie", "mystery", "cookieabout", "mystery", "cookie", "cooky", "look", "like", "get", "home", "get", "picture", "get", "cooky", "friend", "tell", "got", "love", "review", "would", "do", "video", "review", "able", "next", "best", "thing", "post", "review", "think", "along", "picture", "able", "get", "time", "hope", "enjoy", "feel", "free", "leave", "thought", "comment", "try", "yummy", "cooky", "see", "get", "come", "back", "crumble", "cookies", "review", "name", "try", "cooky", "think", "cookie", "would", "prefer", "chocolate", "cookie", "prefer", "topping", "cookie", "would", "get", "thumb", "munch", "good", "lucking", "cookie", "cookie", "taste", "great", "top", "would", "get", "cookie", "thumb", "favorite", "top", "cookie", "would", "get", "cookie", "thumb", "look", "good", "taste", "really", "good", "well", "would", "get", "cookie", "thumb", "rate", "order", "like", "instead", "many", "thumb", "would", "follow", "munch", "honestly", "top", "tie", "place", "opinion", "place", "yesterday", "big", "accomplishment", "drive", "work", "rain", "little", "bit", "wind", "ish", "wind", "constant", "help", "alot", "wind", "speed", "constant", "try", "avoid", "drive", "like", "rain", "yesterday", "avoid", "yesterday", "actually", "drive", "dealt", "time", "puddle", "suck", "wheel", "could", "avoid", "noticed", "wheel", "slip", "drive", "bit", "slow", "also", "attempt", "wear", "new", "rain", "poncho", "get", "work", "well", "blow", "wind", "making", "blocked", "view", "mirror", "feel", "safe", "put", "deal", "rain", "stop", "take", "mention", "pretty", "much", "soak", "good", "bit", "point", "think", "could", "do", "without", "alot", "encouragement", "friend", "everything", "avoid", "remind", "others", "drive", "thing", "like", "daily", "moped", "well", "much", "spend", "driving", "mean", "money", "waste", "point", "try", "good", "get", "experience", "confidence", "drive", "rain", "like", "yesterday", "well", "wind", "also", "drive", "general", "help", "experience", "confidence", "short", "video", "see", "rain", "yesterday", "well", "understand", "drive", "numb", "try", "process", "loss", "yesterday", "also", "still", "try", "deal", "mom", "pass", "well", "pass", "away", "kinda", "lose", "trouble", "deal", "right", "already", "hit", "mom", "early", "week", "loss", "yesterday", "make", "deal", "mom", "pass", "even", "hard", "year", "easy", "post", "make", "right", "get", "news", "amaze", "see", "picture", "birthday", "memory", "video", "https", "youtube", "com", "short", "mpuyjqdyu", "feature", "share", "pass", "away", "even", "would", "next", "month", "may", "th", "wife", "without", "year", "good", "know", "together", "love", "miss", "much", "see", "soon", "get", "something", "week", "stress", "worried", "filling", "paper", "work", "also", "work", "uber", "eats", "nice", "weather", "check", "mop", "hear", "thursday", "morning", "really", "would", "love", "mop", "back", "find", "part", "time", "job", "even", "full", "time", "job", "place", "thing", "go", "back", "burner", "try", "stress", "need", "money", "come", "currently", "get", "wrong", "give", "hour", "lately", "still", "consistent", "cover", "base", "find", "something", "work", "well", "busy", "week", "week", "really", "hop", "get", "everything", "do", "need", "think", "today", "stock", "yarn", "get", "thing", "like", "often", "get", "yesterday", "even", "way", "home", "working", "hour", "hour", "sleep", "really", "make", "day", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "http", "www", "twitch", "tv", "breakmydreams", "wish", "still", "around", "talk", "could", "use", "advice", "situation", "currently", "know", "right", "thing", "ready", "yet", "scar", "lose", "everything", "safety", "net", "anything", "thing", "work", "postpone", "need", "situation", "prove", "ok", "without", "lose", "everything", "safety", "net", "played", "another", "new", "game", "honestly", "say", "love", "somewhat", "addict", "livestreamed", "ride", "work", "morning", "bad", "january", "goal", "well", "month", "earnings", "see", "actually", "alot", "well", "month", "january", "happy", "see", "hope", "continue", "march", "january", "february", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "get", "pay", "via", "paypal", "instantly", "site", "play", "instant", "win", "game", "slot", "game", "also", "get", "daily", "login", "bonus", "every", "hour", "onlyfans", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spank", "model", "work", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "want", "make", "post", "reward", "straight", "talk", "costumer", "would", "think", "straight", "talk", "costumer", "soon", "member", "yet", "feel", "free", "sign", "join", "straight", "talk", "enroll", "use", "referral", "code", "ccjk", "get", "free", "month", "service", "sign", "today", "feel", "like", "sometimes", "people", "costumer", "forget", "reward", "page", "win", "point", "add", "account", "use", "free", "monthly", "minute", "short", "money", "month", "month", "want", "put", "phone", "bill", "money", "towards", "another", "bill", "put", "towards", "something", "fun", "spin", "wheel", "prize", "avaliable", "wheel", "currently", "play", "every", "hour", "show", "morning", "play", "free", "perk", "well", "local", "discount", "choose", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "account", "different", "way", "redeem", "point", "account", "favorite", "use", "use", "free", "service", "plan", "month", "short", "money", "phone", "help", "reward", "goal", "set", "progress", "towards", "far", "time", "play", "game", "time", "play", "laptop", "best", "rank", "far", "game", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "deliver", "delivery", "uber", "eats", "photo", "work", "today", "nice", "outside", "today", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "get", "pay", "via", "paypal", "instantly", "use", "app", "since", "payment", "proofs", "blogged", "free", "app", "get", "cash", "back", "gas", "use", "promo", "code", "get", "extra", "gal", "bonus", "purchase", "http", "upside", "app", "link", "pahhrgcaxbthe", "reason", "save", "much", "someone", "car", "mop", "cost", "alot", "fill", "get", "anywhere", "back", "fill", "gas", "tank", "complain", "add", "use", "cashback", "add", "back", "bank", "account", "awesome", "reward", "choose", "look", "wash", "cloth", "look", "dish", "cloth", "come", "right", "place", "right", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "get", "pay", "via", "paypal", "instantly", "use", "app", "since", "payment", "proofs", "blogged", "look", "soap", "saver", "bag", "need", "quick", "easy", "gift", "someone", "come", "right", "place", "right", "http", "ko", "fi", "com", "excite", "day", "yesterday", "customer", "think", "give", "bill", "owe", "give", "manager", "audit", "verify", "correct", "lady", "still", "go", "owe", "wrong", "want", "number", "regional", "manager", "complain", "otherwise", "today", "ca", "talk", "another", "kidney", "stone", "see", "make", "another", "cashout", "reward", "mainly", "earn", "watch", "video", "complete", "survey", "play", "game", "complete", "discover", "item", "search", "web", "promo", "code", "shop", "online", "lot", "reward", "choose", "besides", "well", "search", "make", "extra", "money", "want", "make", "earning", "online", "full", "time", "job", "site", "definitely", "join", "head", "link", "join", "today", "goal", "want", "reach", "channel", "http", "www", "twitch", "tv", "breakmydreams", "year", "reach", "follower", "captain", "currently", "followers", "away", "goal", "reach", "twitch", "affiliate", "still", "need", "reach", "average", "viewer", "late", "cashout", "current", "january", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "would", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "current", "today", "reward", "option", "well", "counting", "redemption", "make", "reward", "reward", "since", "october", "let", "go", "walk", "twitch", "stream", "breakmydreamswatch", "stream", "game", "craft", "outdoor", "activity", "https", "www", "twitch", "tv", "breakmydreams", "want", "take", "moment", "show", "late", "crochet", "project", "finish", "make", "yesterday", "love", "try", "yet", "plan", "soon", "want", "see", "good", "job", "clean", "last", "long", "one", "buy", "save", "money", "long", "run", "use", "couple", "back", "one", "well", "reusable", "swiffer", "mop", "cover", "make", "video", "show", "well", "head", "watch", "video", "think", "would", "use", "join", "today", "get", "daily", "login", "bonus", "every", "hour", "see", "currently", "wait", "nd", "day", "get", "tomorrow", "morning", "like", "let", "bonus", "log", "save", "start", "play", "game", "game", "tend", "good", "instant", "win", "game", "stick", "get", "sweeps", "money", "cashout", "redeem", "sent", "bank", "account", "cash", "time", "sure", "many", "right", "hand", "guess", "time", "really", "excite", "see", "year", "fully", "track", "online", "earnings", "head", "post", "december", "see", "last", "year", "bad", "start", "year", "want", "good", "earnings", "february", "january", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "mainly", "earn", "unlock", "phone", "watch", "videos", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "earn", "deliver", "food", "costumer", "bike", "regular", "electric", "scooter", "walk", "earn", "complete", "offer", "ptc", "survey", "videos", "promo", "code", "contest", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "use", "app", "almost", "year", "believe", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "cashout", "might", "less", "tend", "wait", "till", "cashout", "see", "recent", "payment", "proof", "wait", "end", "month", "cashout", "cashout", "option", "paypal", "app", "referral", "option", "sign", "survey", "earn", "site", "use", "make", "money", "make", "app", "find", "use", "phone", "actually", "sure", "phone", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "get", "pay", "via", "paypal", "instantly", "use", "app", "since", "payment", "proofs", "blogged", "keep", "power", "http", "gofund", "aceeb", "work", "try", "help", "keep", "power", "family", "member", "please", "donate", "ca", "please", "share", "case", "someone", "else", "know", "donate", "help", "donation", "receive", "much", "apricated", "disclaimer", "choc", "full", "available", "shop", "drive", "thru", "online", "pickup", "delivery", "participate", "shop", "subject", "product", "availability", "offer", "available", "select", "grocery", "store", "supply", "last", "visit", "https", "www", "krispykreme", "com", "locate", "location", "search", "grocery", "find", "close", "participate", "location", "hersheys", "chocolate", "chip", "caramel", "unglazed", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "dip", "hersheys", "caramel", "flavor", "icing", "cover", "semi", "sweet", "chip", "heart", "sprinkle", "hersheys", "chocolate", "icing", "drizzle", "hersheys", "double", "chocolate", "kiss", "doughnut", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "hersheys", "milk", "chocolate", "filling", "dip", "hersheys", "chocolate", "icing", "cover", "hersheys", "mini", "milk", "chocolate", "kisses", "hersheys", "pick", "doughnut", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "dip", "hersheys", "chocolate", "icing", "decorate", "buttercream", "ice", "rise", "hersheys", "heart", "shape", "doughnut", "fill", "hersheys", "strawberry", "flavor", "dip", "red", "icing", "cover", "white", "chip", "heart", "sprinkle", "blend", "filled", "valentine", "day", "heart", "doughnut", "heart", "shape", "fill", "doughnut", "dip", "red", "icing", "decorate", "day", "sprinkle", "doughnut", "available", "krispy", "kreme", "ct", "valentine", "available", "select", "grocery", "store", "well", "select", "convenience", "store", "ends", "strawberry", "iced", "doughnut", "original", "glazed", "doughnut", "dip", "ice", "top", "sprinkle", "blend", "ends", "enter", "today", "ends", "prize", "award", "excellent", "condition", "valued", "second", "place", "enjoy", "metal", "thermometer", "excellent", "condition", "valued", "third", "place", "rare", "cooler", "insert", "embossed", "tin", "sign", "good", "condition", "valued", "prize", "category", "purchase", "necessary", "enter", "win", "must", "resident", "excluding", "ri", "age", "old", "enter", "void", "prohibit", "law", "see", "official", "rules", "detail", "sign", "sign", "today", "enter", "today", "canon", "eos", "giants", "full", "frame", "mirrorless", "camera", "pack", "punch", "predecessor", "affordable", "price", "tag", "give", "bit", "output", "fully", "articulate", "monitor", "heft", "use", "canons", "dslrs", "internally", "capture", "video", "feature", "canons", "industry", "lead", "dual", "pixel", "cmos", "autofocus", "paired", "camera", "innovative", "lens", "mount", "adapter", "use", "lens", "brand", "new", "give", "camera", "away", "lucky", "winner", "competition", "open", "worldwide", "forget", "complete", "entry", "bonus", "entry", "nt", "access", "competition", "social", "channel", "email", "communication", "wo", "nt", "select", "winner", "enter", "today", "ends", "enter", "chance", "win", "skincare", "prize", "winter", "giveaway", "purchase", "necessary", "enter", "resident", "year", "age", "old", "enter", "today", "oled", "could", "earn", "entry", "win", "awesome", "prize", "carbellion", "eclipse", "records", "complete", "action", "gain", "bonus", "entry", "share", "contest", "detail", "friends", "enter", "st", "place", "qty", "oled", "carbellion", "tee", "shirt", "sticker", "place", "qty", "carbellion", "tee", "shirt", "sticker", "cd", "enter", "today", "subscribe", "win", "cozy", "mystery", "bookworm", "basket", "prize", "kindlecat", "lovers", "kindletea", "lovers", "gift", "basketprize", "kindlecoffee", "lovers", "gift", "basketprize", "kindlerelaxation", "gift", "basketprize", "kindleself", "care", "enter", "email", "address", "consent", "receive", "email", "contest", "open", "resident", "find", "updated", "sorry", "late", "fell", "behind", "online", "earnings", "well", "track", "money", "get", "part", "time", "job", "september", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earnings", "catch", "last", "earnings", "post", "really", "sure", "goal", "december", "earn", "safe", "let", "say", "earn", "money", "general", "also", "want", "say", "year", "make", "entire", "year", "time", "ever", "track", "online", "earnings", "proud", "also", "happy", "total", "year", "tell", "go", "work", "improve", "earnings", "also", "able", "follow", "along", "journey", "post", "monthly", "blog", "post", "like", "help", "keep", "track", "earnings", "january", "february", "march", "april", "may", "june", "july", "august", "september", "october", "november", "december", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spank", "model", "work", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "late", "payment", "proof", "site", "earn", "lot", "different", "offer", "ptc", "survey", "videos", "lot", "run", "contest", "every", "month", "well", "daily", "payment", "need", "cash", "earn", "total", "use", "speak", "generally", "regard", "moderate", "deep", "almost", "trace", "like", "condition", "experience", "submissive", "intense", "erotic", "interaction", "subspace", "deep", "go", "subspace", "experience", "subspace", "easily", "hard", "get", "answer", "subspace", "quite", "time", "year", "point", "start", "zone", "float", "everything", "far", "away", "super", "far", "could", "speak", "anymore", "awhile", "scene", "end", "find", "subspace", "hard", "get", "hate", "love", "subspace", "alot", "personally", "something", "take", "alot", "put", "think", "part", "come", "people", "play", "entered", "subspace", "freak", "reaction", "scene", "change", "stop", "scene", "bring", "without", "let", "enjoy", "subspace", "enjoy", "feel", "like", "sort", "unconscious", "block", "go", "subspace", "want", "playing", "experience", "change", "happen", "sub", "enters", "subspace", "freak", "pull", "immediately", "without", "able", "enjoy", "still", "scene", "sub", "enters", "subspace", "let", "enjoy", "long", "get", "deep", "well", "let", "top", "enjoy", "scene", "well", "hopefully", "enter", "really", "want", "next", "place", "long", "term", "place", "call", "home", "worry", "move", "month", "year", "fun", "stressful", "current", "lease", "end", "end", "june", "birthday", "month", "pretty", "sure", "move", "end", "owner", "talk", "want", "sell", "move", "decided", "roommate", "upstairs", "want", "stay", "last", "year", "college", "wish", "friend", "would", "willing", "get", "apartment", "together", "couple", "year", "felt", "like", "home", "try", "figure", "realistic", "goal", "work", "next", "month", "year", "get", "ready", "lease", "end", "end", "june", "save", "money", "move", "save", "money", "next", "payment", "next", "room", "want", "something", "though", "start", "look", "new", "place", "room", "see", "need", "try", "avoid", "close", "lease", "end", "place", "till", "last", "minute", "like", "last", "time", "place", "like", "want", "homeless", "close", "homeless", "stressful", "time", "like", "wish", "boyfriend", "help", "expense", "get", "good", "living", "arrangement", "sigh", "honestly", "sure", "want", "boyfriend", "yet", "kinda", "like", "single", "guy", "kinda", "complicate", "well", "sighs", "epic", "barnes", "noble", "email", "day", "leftenter", "today", "enter", "chance", "win", "bundle", "paperback", "popular", "fantasy", "authors", "time", "winner", "also", "receive", "noble", "email", "gift", "cardbook", "series", "include", "including", "seriesr", "jordan", "wheel", "time", "books", "sanderson", "storm", "light", "archive", "books", "hobb", "farseer", "trilogyr", "riftwar", "saga", "entrance", "also", "receive", "free", "ebook", "copy", "epic", "fantasy", "prequel", "sure", "download", "link", "send", "emailenter", "free", "egift", "card", "day", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "card", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "card", "mother", "day", "day", "leftenter", "today", "egift", "card", "father", "day", "ends", "enter", "today", "egift", "card", "prime", "day", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "th", "july", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "back", "school", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "halloween", "ends", "enter", "today", "egift", "card", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "cyber", "monday", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "christmas", "day", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "ends", "enter", "today", "enter", "free", "egift", "card", "valentines", "enter", "today", "paul", "subscriber", "giveaway", "play", "trade", "guitars", "enter", "today", "help", "play", "grow", "reward", "lucky", "winner", "seriously", "incredible", "give", "away", "play", "reach", "subscriber", "link", "sfw", "link", "spot", "make", "easy", "fan", "mine", "find", "work", "online", "sexworker", "late", "cashout", "current", "january", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "would", "like", "earn", "phone", "like", "head", "link", "sign", "current", "today", "reward", "option", "well", "counting", "redemption", "make", "reward", "reward", "since", "october", "officially", "year", "honestly", "best", "thing", "life", "many", "reason", "excite", "year", "dream", "happen", "actually", "happen", "miss", "cat", "though", "hope", "well", "ex", "boyfriend", "otherwise", "excite", "still", "make", "goal", "happen", "able", "thank", "amaze", "best", "friend", "help", "get", "well", "introduce", "another", "amazing", "best", "friend", "life", "without", "think", "would", "live", "amaze", "another", "site", "creator", "want", "join", "give", "try", "see", "success", "well", "success", "would", "like", "check", "content", "head", "link", "today", "see", "page", "note", "page", "much", "content", "right", "join", "got", "accept", "creator", "today", "would", "like", "creator", "head", "link", "today", "join", "would", "like", "learn", "head", "blog", "post", "today", "note", "link", "post", "maybe", "referral", "link", "get", "small", "discount", "money", "back", "join", "use", "put", "back", "make", "content", "work", "get", "ever", "set", "quad", "game", "since", "lucky", "enough", "catch", "video", "want", "keep", "highlight", "remember", "reaction", "well", "watch", "stream", "game", "craft", "live", "come", "across", "today", "offer", "seem", "referral", "link", "play", "couple", "game", "site", "already", "end", "win", "nice", "also", "notice", "complete", "profile", "earn", "also", "give", "free", "daily", "top", "free", "daily", "top", "happen", "est", "also", "become", "premium", "subscriber", "magazine", "get", "unlimited", "supply", "free", "bingo", "session", "site", "day", "week", "hour", "day", "chance", "win", "session", "well", "right", "test", "site", "thanks", "earn", "enough", "redeem", "reward", "get", "say", "reward", "let", "know", "legit", "fun", "site", "kinda", "kill", "time", "fan", "bingo", "like", "cash", "another", "reward", "today", "january", "use", "app", "unlock", "phone", "also", "occasionally", "watch", "video", "earn", "point", "well", "also", "download", "apps", "play", "game", "earn", "extra", "point", "well", "would", "like", "earn", "reward", "unlock", "phone", "well", "like", "head", "link", "today", "sign", "start", "earn", "reward", "show", "different", "way", "earn", "point", "love", "app", "use", "years", "earn", "reward", "mainly", "cashout", "gift", "card", "gift", "card", "one", "tempt", "get", "day", "sorry", "late", "fell", "behind", "online", "earnings", "well", "track", "money", "get", "part", "time", "job", "september", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earnings", "catch", "last", "earnings", "post", "really", "sure", "goal", "november", "earn", "safe", "let", "say", "earn", "money", "general", "january", "february", "march", "april", "may", "june", "july", "august", "september", "october", "november", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "favorite", "apps", "earn", "let", "run", "phone", "every", "week", "earn", "every", "day", "believe", "earn", "extra", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "sorry", "late", "fell", "behind", "online", "earnings", "well", "track", "money", "get", "part", "time", "job", "dollar", "tree", "last", "month", "september", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earnings", "catch", "last", "earnings", "post", "really", "sure", "goal", "october", "earn", "safe", "let", "say", "earn", "money", "general", "january", "february", "march", "april", "may", "june", "july", "august", "september", "october", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "sure", "make", "money", "honest", "cashback", "earn", "offer", "use", "debit", "card", "app", "phone", "send", "question", "answer", "get", "pay", "via", "paypal", "instantly", "deliever", "bike", "electric", "scooter", "walk", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "someone", "live", "matter", "bad", "hurt", "still", "love", "work", "best", "way", "know", "year", "career", "personal", "record", "date", "story", "unconditional", "love", "heartbreak", "hi", "think", "love", "free", "app", "reward", "shop", "brand", "love", "even", "visit", "store", "sign", "code", "get", "bonus", "kick", "use", "code", "easy", "cash", "reward", "time", "since", "start", "use", "app", "back", "july", "reward", "shop", "store", "online", "already", "make", "use", "earn", "reward", "someone", "please", "explain", "change", "requirement", "state", "city", "live", "mind", "cc", "scooter", "sigh", "feel", "like", "able", "mop", "option", "deliver", "would", "able", "actually", "make", "money", "since", "mess", "algorithm", "bike", "walk", "last", "couple", "year", "sigh", "get", "start", "use", "link", "passive", "income", "app", "phone", "computer", "see", "work", "towards", "cashout", "new", "youtube", "video", "review", "water", "dollar", "tree", "sorry", "late", "fell", "behind", "online", "earnings", "well", "track", "money", "get", "part", "time", "job", "dollar", "tree", "month", "september", "work", "try", "catch", "track", "money", "earnings", "catch", "last", "earnings", "post", "goal", "september", "earnings", "well", "make", "goal", "september", "earnings", "january", "february", "march", "april", "may", "june", "july", "august", "september", "earnings", "total", "earn", "online", "site", "apps", "please", "let", "know", "far", "year", "please", "bingo", "site", "let", "choose", "charity", "support", "also", "choose", "cashout", "earnings", "gift", "card", "paypal", "direct", "deposit", "also", "option", "change", "earnings", "back", "coin", "well", "survey", "site", "survey", "computer", "well", "cell", "phone", "pay", "hit", "task", "onlyfans", "page", "free", "page", "pay", "page", "share", "daily", "content", "spank", "model", "work", "sure", "make", "money", "honest", "current", "earn", "charge", "phone", "watch", "video", "listen", "music", "take", "survey", "earn", "game", "well", "instal", "apps", "direct", "deposit", "paypal", "gift", "cards", "total", "know", "post", "sure", "great", "year", "even", "ups", "down", "feel", "like", "ups", "downs", "way", "end", "scared", "hurt", "upset", "unsure", "go", "go", "lose", "confused", "right", "want", "end", "lose", "currently", "love", "live", "right", "since", "close", "downtown", "good", "neighborhood", "tell", "really", "want", "homeless", "honesty", "happen", "living", "time", "happen", "end", "january", "cause", "breakdown", "scar", "really", "good", "friend", "cause", "issue", "friends", "almost", "happen", "time", "last", "year", "middle", "june", "birthday", "get", "really", "lucky", "find", "place", "become", "homeless", "currently", "deal", "scare", "take", "away", "big", "chunk", "income", "come", "work", "part", "time", "hour", "full", "time", "unless", "manager", "sort", "also", "pay", "unless", "manager", "sort", "well", "bring", "much", "need", "mean", "last", "month", "bring", "enough", "pay", "bill", "rent", "good", "left", "enough", "buy", "grocery", "need", "buy", "last", "month", "money", "gas", "mop", "less", "fill", "still", "put", "money", "saving", "put", "money", "stock", "go", "friend", "karoke", "poker", "currently", "cost", "play", "etc", "go", "eat", "friend", "awhile", "also", "able", "go", "vacation", "want", "get", "away", "bit", "try", "think", "stay", "positive", "thing", "go", "end", "work", "money", "situation", "go", "back", "normal", "get", "well", "end", "january", "quite", "bill", "wo", "pay", "scary", "thing", "wo", "money", "pay", "rent", "february", "keep", "post", "thing", "go", "come", "time", "kinda", "need", "get", "head", "kinda", "something", "look", "back", "onto", "future", "well", "see", "go", "overall", "go", "jump", "go", "run", "errand", "procrastinate", "month", "mop", "get", "oil", "change", "do", "fair", "sick", "bit", "also", "struggle", "afraid", "drive", "least", "day", "week", "traffic", "road", "afraid", "drive", "night", "less", "traffic", "deal", "also", "never", "want", "drive", "either", "think", "play", "huge", "role", "struggle", "drive", "go", "work", "year", "also", "go", "work", "get", "driver", "license", "well", "point", "year", "get", "christmas", "video", "hope", "enjoy", "let", "know", "like", "anything", "get", "well", "let", "know", "get", "christmas", "well", "couple", "goal", "want", "give", "work", "year", "work", "driving", "mop", "want", "sit", "around", "waste", "money", "spend", "well", "want", "need", "get", "driving", "experience", "well", "general", "need", "work", "drive", "new", "area", "see", "like", "well", "road", "big", "fan", "need", "work", "feel", "good", "road", "mess", "work", "get", "another", "part", "time", "job", "pay", "ca", "find", "full", "time", "job", "pay", "well", "well", "slack", "etc", "building", "saving", "stock", "want", "money", "future", "well", "emergencies", "etc", "break", "lose", "progress", "make", "since", "move", "live", "getting", "drive", "experience", "car", "go", "get", "license", "getting", "place", "rent", "room", "actually", "space", "miss", "actually", "place", "actually", "call", "home", "actually", "feel", "like", "home", "working", "get", "weight", "health", "back", "good", "place", "energy", "feel", "happy", "slack", "need", "stop", "one", "think", "right", "work", "currently", "year", "past", "well", "want", "work", "general", "want", "life"], "pos": [["check", "v"], ["newest", "a"], ["book", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["cover", "n"], ["paperback", "n"], ["december", "n"], ["author", "n"], ["find", "v"], ["https", "a"], ["amzn", "n"], ["rfacq", "n"], ["enjoyable", "a"], ["podcast", "n"], ["thinking", "v"], ["actually", "r"], ["follow", "v"], ["disciplined", "a"], ["dream", "n"], ["job", "n"], ["instead", "r"], ["always", "r"], ["slacking", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["going", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["awhile", "r"], ["could", "v"], ["actually", "r"], ["make", "v"], ["worth", "a"], ["living", "v"], ["longterm", "a"], ["stop", "a"], ["slacking", "n"], ["going", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["stay", "v"], ["disciplined", "v"], ["another", null], ["kidney", "n"], ["stone", "n"], ["found", "v"], ["yesterday", "n"], ["quite", "r"], ["bit", "r"], ["pain", "a"], ["nauseated", "v"], ["honestly", "r"], ["getting", "v"], ["dealing", "v"], ["kidney", "n"], ["stones", "n"], ["surprise", "r"], ["anymore", "r"], ["live", "a"], ["told", "v"], ["doctor", "n"], ["immediately", "r"], ["seeing", "v"], ["dehydrated", "v"], ["honestly", "r"], ["stay", "v"], ["hydrated", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["surprising", "a"], ["dehydrated", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["however", "r"], ["news", "n"], ["got", "v"], ["huge", "a"], ["wake", "n"], ["call", "n"], ["going", "v"], ["working", "v"], ["changing", "v"], ["things", "n"], ["avoid", "v"], ["getting", "v"], ["worse", "r"], ["honestly", "r"], ["want", "v"], ["anything", "n"], ["health", "n"], ["scare", "n"], ["going", "v"], ["easy", "a"], ["change", "n"], ["need", "v"], ["necessary", "a"], ["also", "r"], ["called", "v"], ["overweight", "r"], ["something", "n"], ["used", "v"], ["fan", "n"], ["hearing", "v"], ["brings", "n"], ["back", "r"], ["memories", "v"], ["bullied", "v"], ["elementary", "a"], ["school", "n"], ["younger", "a"], ["hurts", "n"], ["morning", "n"], ["dealing", "v"], ["earache", "n"], ["hoping", "n"], ["goes", "v"], ["away", "r"], ["soon", "r"], ["get", "v"], ["worse", "a"], ["jobs", "n"], ["look", "v"], ["require", "a"], ["experience", "n"], ["pay", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["get", "v"], ["wrong", "a"], ["love", "v"], ["housekeeping", "v"], ["favorite", "a"], ["cashiering", "v"], ["stocking", "v"], ["favorite", "a"], ["far", "r"], ["housekeeping", "v"], ["paid", "v"], ["hourly", "r"], ["housekeeper", "r"], ["looking", "v"], ["new", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["experience", "n"], ["pay", "n"], ["since", "r"], ["experience", "n"], ["also", "r"], ["need", "v"], ["job", "n"], ["full", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["part", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["ca", "v"], ["make", "v"], ["ends", "n"], ["meet", "v"], ["part", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["would", "v"], ["part", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["jobs", "n"], ["would", "v"], ["actually", "r"], ["give", "v"], ["hours", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["make", "v"], ["work", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["pay", "v"], ["also", "r"], ["would", "v"], ["love", "v"], ["another", null], ["job", "n"], ["got", "v"], ["overtime", "r"], ["would", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["trouble", "n"], ["job", "n"], ["hunting", "v"], ["working", "v"], ["content", "a"], ["creator", "n"], ["online", "a"], ["work", "n"], ["crafting", "v"], ["mystery", "n"], ["shopping", "n"], ["livestreaming", "v"], ["jobs", "n"], ["full", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["actually", "r"], ["pay", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["make", "v"], ["live", "a"], ["hey", "n"], ["check", "n"], ["app", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["money", "n"], ["back", "r"], ["every", null], ["meal", "n"], ["use", "n"], ["link", "n"], ["sign", "n"], ["get", "v"], ["bonus", "v"], ["meal", "a"], ["get", "v"], ["https", "a"], ["seated", "v"], ["app", "a"], ["link", "n"], ["eqeqywzdb", "n"], ["kinda", "n"], ["pickle", "n"], ["work", "n"], ["feel", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["going", "v"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["based", "v"], ["stocking", "n"], ["manager", "n"], ["told", "v"], ["going", "v"], ["start", "n"], ["stockers", "n"], ["going", "v"], ["start", "n"], ["writing", "v"], ["stocking", "v"], ["boxes", "n"], ["hour", "n"], ["normal", "a"], ["stocking", "n"], ["day", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["write", "r"], ["ups", "a"], ["things", "n"], ["put", "v"], ["correct", "a"], ["uboats", "a"], ["pallets", "n"], ["truck", "n"], ["day", "n"], ["based", "v"], ["said", "v"], ["yesterday", "n"], ["likely", "a"], ["wrote", "v"], ["uboat", "a"], ["boxes", "n"], ["meaning", "v"], ["taken", "v"], ["half", "n"], ["hours", "n"], ["complete", "a"], ["took", "v"], ["entire", "a"], ["shift", "n"], ["meaning", "n"], ["super", "n"], ["thin", "a"], ["ice", "n"], ["work", "n"], ["previous", "a"], ["write", "a"], ["ups", "n"], ["going", "v"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["write", "a"], ["stocking", "v"], ["boxes", "n"], ["fast", "r"], ["enough", "r"], ["let", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["overthinking", "v"], ["put", "v"], ["position", "n"], ["post", "n"], ["made", "v"], ["dollar", "n"], ["tree", "n"], ["reddit", "n"], ["page", "n"], ["asking", "v"], ["number", "n"], ["report", "n"], ["violations", "n"], ["annousmously", "r"], ["store", "v"], ["manager", "n"], ["saw", "n"], ["asked", "v"], ["ended", "v"], ["telling", "v"], ["felt", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["violations", "n"], ["text", "v"], ["told", "v"], ["getting", "v"], ["number", "n"], ["case", "n"], ["confident", "a"], ["enough", "r"], ["go", "v"], ["yet", "r"], ["called", "v"], ["anything", "n"], ["said", "v"], ["could", "v"], ["wanted", "v"], ["though", "r"], ["mentioned", "v"], ["wanted", "v"], ["come", "a"], ["waiting", "v"], ["call", "a"], ["mention", "n"], ["stocking", "n"], ["manager", "n"], ["said", "v"], ["feel", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["going", "v"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["write", "v"], ["really", "r"], ["want", "a"], ["happen", "n"], ["reply", "n"], ["yet", "r"], ["fair", "v"], ["yesterday", "n"], ["thanksgiving", "n"], ["mention", "n"], ["wanted", "v"], ["put", "a"], ["truck", "n"], ["days", "n"], ["instead", "r"], ["means", "v"], ["less", "a"], ["chance", "n"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["wrote", "v"], ["stocking", "v"], ["enough", "a"], ["boxes", "n"], ["hour", "n"], ["hate", "v"], ["though", "r"], ["really", "r"], ["need", "v"], ["hours", "n"], ["week", "n"], ["work", "n"], ["hours", "n"], ["work", "v"], ["actually", "r"], ["brought", "v"], ["enough", "a"], ["money", "n"], ["pay", "n"], ["bills", "n"], ["save", "v"], ["money", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["going", "v"], ["lose", "r"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["another", null], ["write", "n"], ["go", "v"], ["back", "r"], ["hours", "n"], ["week", "n"], ["mentioned", "v"], ["would", "v"], ["like", "v"], ["better", "a"], ["training", "n"], ["know", "v"], ["many", "a"], ["boxes", "n"], ["hour", "n"], ["stocking", "v"], ["hour", "n"], ["would", "v"], ["feel", "v"], ["comfortable", "a"], ["stocking", "v"], ["worrying", "a"], ["wrote", "v"], ["losing", "v"], ["job", "n"], ["love", "r"], ["stocking", "v"], ["job", "n"], ["want", "v"], ["continue", "n"], ["working", "v"], ["stocking", "v"], ["actually", "r"], ["like", "r"], ["working", "v"], ["dollar", "n"], ["tree", "n"], ["particuallary", "a"], ["store", "n"], ["working", "v"], ["employees", "n"], ["costumers", "n"], ["know", "v"], ["come", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["sighs", "n"], ["stressing", "v"], ["feeling", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["going", "v"], ["fired", "a"], ["vacation", "n"], ["days", "n"], ["somehow", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["lucky", "a"], ["lose", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["lose", "v"], ["hours", "n"], ["even", "r"], ["though", "r"], ["hours", "n"], ["holiday", "v"], ["going", "v"], ["upset", "a"], ["need", "n"], ["hours", "n"], ["week", "n"], ["hours", "n"], ["week", "n"], ["amazing", "a"], ["past", "a"], ["month", "n"], ["anyways", "n"], ["need", "v"], ["finish", "a"], ["getting", "v"], ["ready", "a"], ["work", "n"], ["morning", "n"], ["needed", "v"], ["get", "n"], ["stressing", "v"], ["crying", "v"], ["super", "a"], ["crappy", "a"], ["week", "n"], ["general", "a"], ["kinda", "n"], ["quiet", "a"], ["hiding", "v"], ["avoiding", "v"], ["people", "n"], ["afraid", "a"], ["take", "v"], ["step", "n"], ["find", "v"], ["better", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["afraid", "a"], ["losing", "v"], ["currently", "r"], ["afraid", "v"], ["find", "v"], ["new", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["lose", "a"], ["jobless", "n"], ["afraid", "a"], ["position", "n"], ["kinda", "n"], ["comfortable", "a"], ["current", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["without", "r"], ["hours", "n"], ["part", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["work", "n"], ["realizing", "v"], ["much", "a"], ["lose", "v"], ["lose", "a"], ["current", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["new", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["work", "n"], ["lose", "v"], ["everything", "n"], ["worked", "v"], ["convince", "a"], ["take", "v"], ["next", "a"], ["step", "n"], ["find", "v"], ["job", "n"], ["pays", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["experience", "n"], ["worth", "n"], ["sighs", "v"], ["recent", "a"], ["cashout", "n"], ["cashed", "v"], ["reward", "n"], ["alot", "n"], ["gift", "n"], ["card", "n"], ["choices", "n"], ["fan", "v"], ["need", "v"], ["current", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["earn", "n"], ["surveys", "n"], ["videos", "v"], ["promo", "n"], ["codes", "n"], ["games", "n"], ["offers", "n"], ["member", "n"], ["yet", "r"], ["would", "v"], ["like", "v"], ["join", "n"], ["head", "n"], ["link", "v"], ["today", "n"], ["join", "v"], ["need", "n"], ["help", "n"], ["joining", "v"], ["let", "v"], ["know", "n"], ["share", "n"], ["earned", "v"], ["recently", "r"], ["see", "v"], ["lifetime", "a"], ["earnings", "n"], ["reminds", "v"], ["playing", "v"], ["fruits", "n"], ["play", "v"], ["heading", "v"], ["https", "n"], ["suikagame", "n"], ["io", "a"], ["think", "v"], ["played", "v"], ["game", "n"], ["yet", "r"], ["watch", "a"], ["stream", "n"], ["games", "n"], ["crafts", "v"], ["live", "a"], ["https", "n"], ["www", "n"], ["twitch", "v"], ["tv", "n"], ["breakmydreams", "n"], ["see", "v"], ["made", "v"], ["another", null], ["cashout", "n"], ["another", null], ["gift", "n"], ["card", "n"], ["mainly", "r"], ["earn", "v"], ["watching", "v"], ["videos", "n"], ["completing", "v"], ["surveys", "n"], ["promo", "v"], ["codes", "n"], ["searching", "v"], ["web", "n"], ["completing", "v"], ["offers", "n"], ["lots", "a"], ["rewards", "n"], ["besides", "r"], ["gift", "n"], ["cards", "n"], ["choose", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["search", "r"], ["making", "v"], ["extra", "a"], ["money", "n"], ["want", "v"], ["make", "n"], ["earning", "n"], ["online", "v"], ["full", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["job", "n"], ["sites", "n"], ["defiantly", "r"], ["join", "v"], ["heading", "v"], ["link", "n"], ["join", "n"], ["today", "n"], ["see", "v"], ["made", "v"], ["another", null], ["cashout", "n"], ["reward", "n"], ["mainly", "r"], ["earn", "v"], ["watching", "v"], ["videos", "n"], ["completing", "v"], ["surveys", "n"], ["playing", "v"], ["games", "n"], ["completing", "v"], ["discover", "r"], ["items", "n"], ["searching", "v"], ["web", "n"], ["promo", "n"], ["codes", "n"], ["shopping", "v"], ["online", "a"], ["lots", "n"], ["rewards", "n"], ["choose", "v"], ["besides", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["search", "v"], ["making", "v"], ["extra", "a"], ["money", "n"], ["want", "v"], ["make", "n"], ["earning", "n"], ["online", "v"], ["full", "a"], ["time", "n"], ["job", "n"], ["sites", "n"], ["definitely", "r"], ["join", "v"], ["heading", "v"], ["link", "n"], ["join", "n"], ["today", "n"], ["know", "v"], ["alone", "r"], ["counting", "v"], ["christmas", "n"], ["gets", "v"], ["closer", "a"], ["know", "n"], ["always", "r"], ["loved", "v"], ["still", "r"], ["love", "v"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["wanted", "v"], ["share", "n"], ["ones", "n"], ["found", "v"], ["hope", "n"], ["enjoy", null], ["let", "n"], ["know", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["gmadelaine", "a"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["premium", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["chocolates", "n"], ["oz", "a"], ["grams", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["ozoriginal", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["imported", "n"], ["dairy", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["chocolatehershey", "n"], ["miniatures", "n"], ["candy", "n"], ["filled", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["nice", "n"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["pieces", "n"], ["peanut", "n"], ["butter", "n"], ["cup", "n"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["days", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["hershey", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["kisses", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendargalerie", "n"], ["marvel", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["days", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["pieces", "n"], ["ounces", "n"], ["blueelf", "n"], ["shelf", "n"], ["milk", "n"], ["chocolate", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["advent", "n"], ["countdown", "n"], ["calendar", "n"], ["oz", "v"], ["note", "n"], ["links", "n"], ["post", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["contain", "v"], ["affiliate", "a"], ["links", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["cost", "n"], ["anything", "n"], ["extra", "a"], ["qualifying", "v"], ["purchase", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["receive", "v"], ["small", "a"], ["commension", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["app", "a"], ["almost", "r"], ["years", "n"], ["believe", "v"], ["favorite", "a"], ["apps", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["let", "v"], ["run", "v"], ["phone", "n"], ["every", null], ["week", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["every", null], ["days", "n"], ["believe", "v"], ["earn", "v"], ["extra", "a"], ["cashout", "n"], ["might", "v"], ["less", "v"], ["tend", "a"], ["wait", "n"], ["till", "n"], ["cashout", "n"], ["see", "v"], ["recent", "a"], ["payment", "n"], ["proof", "n"], ["wait", "a"], ["end", "a"], ["month", "n"], ["cashout", "n"], ["cashout", "n"], ["option", "n"], ["paypal", "n"], ["app", "v"], ["referral", "a"], ["option", "n"], ["signed", "v"], ["survey", "n"], ["earning", "v"], ["sites", "n"], ["use", "v"], ["make", "v"], ["money", "n"], ["made", "v"], ["app", "r"], ["find", "v"], ["use", "n"], ["phones", "n"], ["actually", "r"], ["sure", "a"], ["phones", "n"], ["payment", "n"], ["method", "n"], ["choose", "a"], ["image", "n"], ["mind", "n"], ["since", "r"], ["love", "n"], ["use", "n"], ["alot", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["awhile", "a"], ["cashout", "n"], ["waited", "v"], ["awhile", "a"], ["cash", "n"], ["see", "v"], ["app", "a"], ["let", "v"], ["run", "v"], ["background", "r"], ["devices", "n"], ["check", "v"], ["app", "r"], ["free", "a"], ["points", "n"], ["daily", "a"], ["show", "v"], ["honey", "n"], ["jar", "n"], ["cashout", "n"], ["wo", "v"], ["last", "a"], ["either", null], ["love", "v"], ["apps", "n"], ["let", "v"], ["run", "v"], ["make", "v"], ["money", "n"], ["shows", "n"], ["different", "a"], ["ways", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["points", "n"], ["love", "v"], ["app", "r"], ["using", "v"], ["years", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["rewards", "n"], ["mainly", "r"], ["cashout", "v"], ["gift", "n"], ["cards", "n"], ["gift", "n"], ["cards", "n"], ["ones", "n"], ["tempted", "v"], ["get", "a"], ["day", "n"], ["cashed", "v"], ["another", null], ["reward", "n"], ["today", "n"], ["october", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["app", "a"], ["unlock", "n"], ["phone", "n"], ["also", "r"], ["occasionally", "r"], ["watch", "v"], ["video", "n"], ["earn", "n"], ["points", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["also", "r"], ["download", "n"], ["apps", "a"], ["play", "n"], ["games", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["extra", "a"], ["points", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["would", "v"], ["like", "v"], ["earn", "n"], ["rewards", "n"], ["unlocking", "v"], ["phone", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["like", "r"], ["head", "n"], ["link", "v"], ["today", "n"], ["sign", "a"], ["start", "n"], ["earning", "v"], ["rewards", "n"], ["sighs", "a"], ["comment", "n"], ["earlier", "r"], ["made", "v"], ["think", "v"], ["ex", "a"], ["boyfriend", "v"], ["even", "r"], ["really", "r"], ["sure", "a"], ["made", "v"], ["want", "v"], ["cry", "a"], ["part", "n"], ["still", "r"], ["feelings", "v"], ["ex", "a"], ["boyfriend", "a"], ["wish", "n"], ["able", "a"], ["friends", "n"], ["cut", "v"], ["life", "n"], ["way", "n"], ["left", "v"], ["comment", "n"], ["made", "v"], ["think", "v"], ["sighs", "n"], ["left", "v"], ["wrong", "a"], ["way", "n"], ["wish", "n"], ["could", "v"], ["go", "v"], ["back", "r"], ["leave", "v"], ["correct", "a"], ["way", "n"], ["hurt", "v"], ["badly", "r"], ["ca", "v"], ["learn", "v"], ["ever", "r"], ["get", "v"], ["another", null], ["relationship", "n"], ["thing", "n"], ["guy", "n"], ["fair", "a"], ["though", "r"], ["see", "a"], ["happening", "v"], ["sighs", "n"], ["ex", "a"], ["boyfriend", "v"], ["good", "a"], ["guy", "n"], ["perfect", "v"], ["neither", null], ["still", "r"], ["grown", "v"], ["alot", "n"], ["since", "r"], ["leaving", "v"], ["grew", "v"], ["well", "r"], ["grew", "v"], ["leaving", "v"], ["time", "n"], ["life", "n"], ["needed", "v"], ["learn", "a"], ["adult", "n"], ["independent", "a"], ["thank", "n"], ["also", "r"], ["worst", "v"], ["parts", "n"], ["life", "n"], ["passed", "v"], ["away", "r"], ["yeah", "a"], ["kept", "v"], ["alive", "a"], ["along", "r"], ["cat", "n"], ["wish", "n"], ["still", "r"], ["left", "v"], ["living", "v"], ["stable", "a"], ["fair", "a"], ["sighs", "n"], ["yeah", "v"], ["going", "v"], ["kinda", "n"], ["leave", "v"], ["needed", "v"], ["get", "n"], ["sighs", "n"], ["hoping", "v"], ["mood", "n"], ["headspace", "n"], ["get", "v"], ["memories", "n"], ["ex", "v"], ["boyfriend", "v"], ["messed", "v"], ["honestly", "r"], ["stressed", "v"], ["enough", "r"], ["feeling", "v"], ["like", "r"], ["failing", "v"], ["living", "v"], ["going", "v"], ["lose", "a"], ["worked", "a"], ["things", "n"], ["change", "v"], ["job", "n"], ["wise", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["continuing", "v"], ["make", "v"], ["independent", "a"], ["responsible", "a"], ["adult", "n"], ["choices", "n"], ["feel", "v"], ["like", "r"], ["struggling", "v"], ["still", "r"], ["hate", "v"], ["wo", "v"], ["help", "v"], ["taking", "v"], ["step", "v"], ["new", "a"], ["job", "n"], ["sighs", "n"], ["memories", "n"], ["suck", "v"], ["relationships", "n"], ["suck", "v"], ["adult", "n"], ["sucks", "n"], ["emotions", "n"], ["suck", "v"], ["halloween", "n"], ["coming", "v"], ["big", "a"], ["night", "n"], ["needing", "v"], ["decorations", "n"], ["thought", "v"], ["would", "v"], ["good", "a"], ["thing", "n"], ["share", "n"], ["finds", "v"], ["outdoor", "a"], ["decorations", "n"], ["get", "v"], ["hands", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["pcs", "n"], ["spooky", "n"], ["atmosphere", "n"], ["perfect", "n"], ["festive", "n"], ["home", "n"], ["displaygivalue", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["lantern", "n"], ["string", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["decorative", "n"], ["lanterns", "n"], ["pumpkin", "n"], ["ghost", "n"], ["bat", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["string", "n"], ["plug", "n"], ["ft", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["white", "n"], ["ghost", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["leds", "n"], ["operated", "n"], ["lighted", "n"], ["holiday", "n"], ["displays", "n"], ["remote", "n"], ["spooky", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["warm", "n"], ["yellow", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["genswin", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["flameless", "n"], ["votive", "n"], ["candles", "n"], ["color", "n"], ["changing", "n"], ["battery", "n"], ["operated", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["tealight", "n"], ["candles", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["home", "n"], ["decoration", "n"], ["gifts", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["battery", "n"], ["included", "v"], ["pack", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["party", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["set", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["window", "n"], ["clings", "n"], ["bat", "n"], ["wall", "n"], ["decal", "n"], ["perfect", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorationsfunpeny", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["inch", "n"], ["wooden", "n"], ["nutcrackers", "n"], ["figures", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["table", "n"], ["fireplace", "n"], ["desk", "n"], ["man", "n"], ["jack", "n"], ["lantern", "n"], ["pumpkin", "n"], ["candy", "n"], ["bucketaerwo", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decoration", "n"], ["black", "n"], ["lace", "n"], ["spiderweb", "n"], ["fireplace", "n"], ["mantle", "n"], ["scarf", "n"], ["cm", "n"], ["inchvanthylit", "n"], ["black", "n"], ["spooky", "n"], ["tree", "n"], ["glittered", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["purple", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["bat", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["battery", "n"], ["powered", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["tree", "n"], ["decoration", "n"], ["tabletop", "n"], ["home", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["ft", "n"], ["timer", "n"], ["meonum", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["candles", "n"], ["battery", "n"], ["operated", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["flameless", "n"], ["candles", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["skeleton", "n"], ["hands", "n"], ["hold", "n"], ["candle", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["centerpiece", "n"], ["tables", "n"], ["fireplace", "n"], ["party", "n"], ["decorhalloween", "n"], ["ghost", "n"], ["candle", "n"], ["scene", "n"], ["bowl", "n"], ["candle", "n"], ["glow", "n"], ["dark", "n"], ["lantern", "n"], ["fall", "n"], ["scented", "n"], ["holiday", "n"], ["decoration", "n"], ["gift", "n"], ["set", "n"], ["note", "n"], ["links", "v"], ["post", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["contain", "v"], ["affiliate", "a"], ["links", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["cost", "n"], ["anything", "n"], ["extra", "a"], ["qualifying", "v"], ["purchase", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["receive", "v"], ["small", "a"], ["commension", "n"], ["get", "n"], ["paid", "v"], ["healthy", "a"], ["connect", "n"], ["apps", "a"], ["start", "n"], ["earning", "v"], ["head", "n"], ["link", "n"], ["today", "n"], ["sign", "v"], ["give", "a"], ["example", "n"], ["apps", "n"], ["connect", "n"], ["evidation", "n"], ["earn", "n"], ["points", "n"], ["connected", "v"], ["mine", "a"], ["apps", "n"], ["connect", "n"], ["use", "n"], ["see", "n"], ["earned", "v"], ["total", "a"], ["app", "n"], ["since", "r"], ["latest", "a"], ["cashout", "n"], ["current", "n"], ["october", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["charging", "v"], ["phone", "n"], ["watching", "v"], ["videos", "n"], ["listening", "v"], ["music", "n"], ["taking", "v"], ["surveys", "n"], ["earn", "v"], ["games", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["installing", "v"], ["apps", "r"], ["would", "v"], ["like", "v"], ["earn", "v"], ["phone", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["head", "n"], ["link", "v"], ["sign", "n"], ["current", "n"], ["today", "n"], ["reward", "n"], ["options", "n"], ["well", "r"], ["counting", "v"], ["redemption", "n"], ["made", "v"], ["rewards", "n"], ["rewards", "n"], ["since", "r"], ["october", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["coming", "v"], ["big", "a"], ["night", "n"], ["needing", "v"], ["decorations", "n"], ["thought", "v"], ["would", "v"], ["good", "a"], ["thing", "n"], ["share", "n"], ["finds", "v"], ["outdoor", "a"], ["decorations", "n"], ["get", "v"], ["hands", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["joyin", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["decorationsjoyin", "n"], ["pack", "n"], ["hanging", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["skeleton", "n"], ["ghosts", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["grim", "n"], ["reapers", "n"], ["hanging", "n"], ["ghosts", "n"], ["cute", "n"], ["flying", "v"], ["ghost", "n"], ["front", "n"], ["yard", "n"], ["patio", "n"], ["lawn", "n"], ["garden", "n"], ["party", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["sqft", "n"], ["spider", "n"], ["webs", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["bonus", "n"], ["fake", "n"], ["spiders", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["party", "n"], ["suppliesgivalue", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["decorative", "n"], ["lanterns", "n"], ["pumpkin", "n"], ["ghost", "n"], ["bat", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["string", "n"], ["plug", "n"], ["ft", "n"], ["connectable", "n"], ["indoor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["orange", "n"], ["pumpkin", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["scary", "n"], ["zombie", "n"], ["vampire", "n"], ["graves", "n"], ["lawn", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["beware", "n"], ["warning", "n"], ["stakes", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["scary", "n"], ["giant", "n"], ["spider", "n"], ["fake", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["window", "n"], ["projector", "n"], ["christmas", "n"], ["birthday", "n"], ["dayspider", "n"], ["web", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decoration", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["purple", "n"], ["led", "n"], ["light", "n"], ["ft", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["yard", "n"], ["outsidepcs", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decorations", "n"], ["outdoor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["witch", "n"], ["hats", "n"], ["ft", "v"], ["lighting", "v"], ["modes", "n"], ["string", "n"], ["lights", "n"], ["tree", "n"], ["patio", "n"], ["yard", "n"], ["party", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["decor", "n"], ["note", "n"], ["links", "v"], ["post", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["contain", "v"], ["affiliate", "a"], ["links", "n"], ["using", "v"], ["cost", "n"], ["anything", "n"], ["extra", "a"], ["qualifying", "v"], ["purchase", "n"], ["may", "v"], ["receive", "v"], ["small", "a"], ["commension", "n"], ["follow", "a"], ["subscribe", "n"], ["subscribing", "v"], ["get", "v"], ["sub", "a"], ["live", "a"], ["streams", "n"], ["like", "r"], ["song", "n"], ["requests", "n"], ["direct", "a"], ["messages", "n"], ["comment", "v"], ["response", "n"], ["shoutout", "n"], ["behind", "r"], ["scenes", "n"], ["video", "n"], ["costs", "n"], ["month", "n"], ["subscribe", "v"], ["hope", "n"], ["see", "n"], ["soon", "r"], ["subscribe", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["coming", "v"], ["big", "a"], ["night", "n"], ["needing", "v"], ["costumes", "n"], ["thought", "v"], ["would", "v"], ["good", "a"], ["thing", "n"], ["share", "n"], ["finds", "v"], ["costumes", "n"], ["get", "v"], ["hands", "n"], ["time", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["women", "n"], ["hippie", "n"], ["costume", "n"], ["set", "n"], ["halloween", "n"], ["hippie", "n"], ["dress", "n"], ["bell", "n"], ["bottom", "n"], ["boho", "n"], ["flared", "n"], ["pant", "n"], ["dress", 